<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<!DOCTYPE moreovercontentdump SYSTEM "http://d.moreover.com/click/dtds/metabase005b.dtd">
	<moreovercontentdump>
        <article id="_3860761814">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[やさしい言葉のかけ方 - トピさんが参ってしまう前に。]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[　32歳男性です。妻と子どもが一人います。 

　妻の産後うつがひどく困っています。特に罵倒がひどく、収入が少ない、学歴が低いなどなど、妻の私への言葉が激しすぎるため精神的にまいっています。以前から口は悪いほうだったのですが、妊娠してから拍車がかかり、かれこれ一年以上一日一度は罵られる生活が続いています。 

　よくこういうときにやさしい言葉をかけてあげるのがよいと聞きますが、正直に言ってどういう言葉をかけていいのかわかりません。何をいっても否定されるので言葉を発する気力がなくなってくるのですが、黙っていたら黙っていたで叱責されます。正直妻と話したり妻のメールをみること自体に恐怖心があります。罵倒の言葉も聞くに堪えないものばかりで、ついカッとなって言い返してしまうときもあります。 

言い返してしまう未熟な自分にも嫌気がさすのですが、どういう言葉をかけてあげればいいのかわからず、本当に途方に暮れています。何かアドバイスをいただけないでしょうか。]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761814&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/f0b5bb661292eb7f61be7712a0174014?ul=XFtq.Xdp.TH6qW6K3SkE8AdErfGHz99nsT72ushFLlj0PoBKV9bYKfAGdHgOmVDsgcY9.CfHq07xIUvIJvm7Yn20Kkec</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>10</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761819">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[鬼門！ロールケーキ - 間違えました。]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[以前、親戚の子どもたちに食べてもらうために、 

こちらでシュークリームの作り方をご指南いただいた男です。 

その子どもたちが我が家に遊びになることになり、先日、 

「チョコのロールケーキ作って！」という特命が下りました。 

子どもたちの可愛さにほおがゆるんだ反面、私にとって、 

ロールケーキは失敗続きの「鬼門」であって、頭を抱えています。 

だって、ふくらまないんです。敷き紙から上手くはがれないんです。 

先日練習したのですが、ココアと薄力粉を生地に混ぜ入れる段階で 

ダマになってしまい、ダマを消そうと思って混ぜたら、 

生地が見る見るしぼんでいきました・・・。 

他にも分からない点として、 

○人肌に温めて混ぜるというが、どの段階まで人肌の温度をキープすれば良い？ 

（泡立てる最初だけ？　粉類を入れるまで？　オーブンに入れるまで？） 

○気泡をなるべくつぶさずに、薄力粉やカカオなど粉類を生地にうまく混ぜ入れるには？ 

（先日、恥ずかしながら、某デパートのプロの実演クッキングを見に行きました。 

定番の「さっくり混ぜろ」というのは間違いで、粉がなくなるまで良く混ぜても構わない 

混ぜる際は、ボウルを回しながら周りから混ぜて上から落とすようになど） 

○敷き紙からはがせるようにするには？ 

（焼きが足りない？　天板からすぐ離す？） 

素人が難しいことをやるべきじゃないのですが、子どもたちがチョコの生地を熱望していて、 

ココア粉末を混ぜ込むことは避けられません。 

ちなみに家族は、「所詮お前は素人。無駄なことはやめておけ。プロのロールケーキを 

買ってくれば済む話」と、極めて理性的かつ現実的な人々です。 

もとより素人風情であることは百も承知ですが、黙って引き下がりたくありません。 

上記の点を含め、ご指南よろしくお願いいたします。 

ユーザーID：6761220266 

お気に入り登録数：17 

古いレス順 

レス数：15本 

タイトル 

投稿者 

はな 

2010年12月21日 11:04 

ココアと薄力粉は別々に入れてますか？ 

生地に混ぜいれる段階ではなく、ふるう時に一緒にしておきましょう。 

卵をあわ立てる時に、湯煎で溶かしたチョコレートを入れる人もいます。 

半量のメレンゲを残しておき、粉を入れた後から加える人もいます。 

メレンゲはツノが立つほどあわ立ててますか？ 

オーブンは余熱してますよね？ 

＞ダマになってしまい、ダマを消そうと思って混ぜたら 

むきになって、こねくり回しちゃいましたか？ 

混ぜ過ぎはせっかくあわ立てた卵白の泡がなくなるので禁物です。 

＞敷き紙からはがせるようにするには 

敷き紙にバターは塗ってますか？ 

敷き紙だけではなく、生地そのものにも溶かしバターを入れる人もいます。 

定番の「切るようにボールの底から、手早くサックリ」の説明は 

実際、その表現で成功してる人はいるのです。 

ですが、その表現ではうまくできない人はいて 

否定することは、別な方法を強く印象づけられます。 

どうやって混ぜるかなぁ…とやってみると 

私はサックリ式なのですが、同じやり方を 

「ボウルを回しながら〜」とも説明できるな、と思いましたよ。 

ユーザーID：9501936979 

はな 

2010年12月21日 11:13 

タマゴのサイズは？ 

白身が多いのでＬを使った方がいいと思います。 

カステラなら、黄身タップリの濃厚さも魅力ですが 

タマゴのサイズは（重さの違い）は、ほぼ白身の量です。 

黄身の大きさはたいしてかわらないので 

もしＳを使ってるなら 

黄身に対しての白身の量が少ないので、その分メレンゲも少ないのでは？ 

後からあわせる生地を分けておかないなら 

粉は生地に１度に入れず、３回くらいに分けたほうがいいです。 

混ぜるのが苦手かも？と思うなら 

生地を２つに分けて、粉をまざった後で、残りの生地を加える方が 

つぶれずに残る泡が多いかも…。 

なんだか、まとまりのない文章でごめんなさい。 

ユーザーID：9501936979 

ぴじー 

2010年12月21日 12:08 

生地に粉を混ぜる時の基本は、タイトルどおり 

「クルっとまわして、１，２、３」 

です。 

左手でボール、右手でゴムヘラを持ちます。 

ゴムヘラをボールの内側に沿って、生地をクルっと混ぜます。 

この時、ボールを抑えた左手は右手と逆方向に動かします。 

つまり、右手は時計方向、左手は反時計方向に回しています。 

回したら、ゴムべらで、生地を縦方向に１、２、３　と切ります。 

数回繰り返すと、生地をこねずに綺麗に混ぜることができますよ。 

試してみてください。 

ユーザーID：6301933489 

マッツィー 

2010年12月21日 12:25 

こんにちは。 

レシピは本を参考にしていただくとして、人肌に温めるのは全卵を立てるときです。溶かしバターを加えるときも、温度が低いと固まりやすいので温かい状態がいいです。 

ココアが入るとどうしても気泡がつぶれやすくなるので、あらかじめ薄力粉とよく合わせてふるっておき、手早く混ぜましょう。混ぜ方はご指摘の通りです。 

敷き紙からはがれにくいのは、多分焼きすぎだと思います。生地が薄いので焼き加減は非常に微妙です。これは経験でつかむしかないと思います。 

ではご健闘を祈ります。 

ユーザーID：7386224656 

朝日 

2010年12月21日 12:39 

まず、ココアパウダーと薄力粉は合わせてふるいに2回かけてますか？ 

ダマができたのは、ふるいが足りなかったか一度に大量投入したせいだと思います。 

粉類を入れるときは出来るだけ少量ずつ、最低でも3回に分けます。 

湯煎をするのは泡立てるところまででいいと思いますよ。 

あたためるということは共立てのレシピでしょうか？ 

卵白を別に泡立てて後で混ぜるレシピのほうが素人向きかもしれません。 

その場合は卵白も3回に分けて入れます。 

混ぜ方のコツは、左手でボウルをまわしつつ、右手は手首を返すようにして、ご飯を混ぜる要領でやると上手くできます。 

敷紙にはバターをたっぷり塗っておけばOKです。 

中のクリームは、ぜひ動物性油脂で脂肪分２５％以上のものを使ってみてください。 

よく使われている植物性油脂のものとは格の違う本物の美味しさをお子さん達に知ってもらいたいです。 

タカナシの乳脂肪分４０％くらいのものがおすすめです。 

ただ、脂肪分が多いと泡立てたときに硬くなりすぎることがあるので、気をつけてください。 

がんばってくださいね。 

ユーザーID：6110174942 

はな 

2010年12月21日 12:50 

普通のスポンジはクリア出来てますか？ 

私はチョコシロップを最後に入れてもうひとまぜ 

ココア使いません。 

ロールケーキの敷紙はリ○ド等のホットクッキングシートがオススメです。 

共立てならしっかり湯煎しながら泡立て→少し冷める迄湯煎から離して泡立て 

別立てでも卵黄は共立ての要領で 

泡立てをしっかりとが成功の鍵だと 

粉に片栗粉かコーンスターチを大匙山に1 混ぜます 

仕上がりが良いと思います 

ユーザーID：7913325635 

taa 

2010年12月21日 15:49 

私はもっぱらスポンジケーキばかり焼いているのですがね。、基本は同じだと思います。 

ココアと薄力粉は一緒に事前にふるってありますものね？ 

ざざっと一点にいれずに、泡立てた卵の全面にふわっとのせる感じで入れますが、だまになることってあまりないと思うので（粉が多いんでしょうか？）、 

粉のグラムもあっているのでしたら不思議ですね。 

卵をほぐし砂糖を入れ泡立てる時に、下に湯煎のボールをおきます。 

ハンドミキサーで泡立てながら、生地に指を突っ込んで人肌になったら湯煎をはずして更に泡立てます。丁度砂糖が溶けた感じで人肌になります。 

ボールを左手で回し、右手でへらを持ってさっくり混ぜていきます。混ぜる回数は最初から最後まで25回位です。これで、泡もつぶさずに、粉もきちんと混ざっています。大きく「の」の字を書くように、底から、脇からさっくり混ぜます。 

私は上から落とすように混ぜたことはないですが、失敗したことはないです。良く混ぜたこともないんですが、スポンジはふわふわにできます。 

敷き紙からはがれないのは、やはり焼きが足りないのかなと思います。]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761819&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/0fa688e93ca9f2d0ec377308eebfdb47?ul=Lm60rla1vBvU0wxuNRXKE1a9Qt9_tPTCiaRzifTRav1W9OIuF.pl1YZIXCDDpmrcfOVd3dAWBW6wuL4UAY1EW_n_DVTk</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>11</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761821">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="French">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Le roi saoudien aurait quitté l'hôpital en bonne santé]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Le roi Abdallah d'Arabie saoudite a quitté en bonne santé l'hôpital de New York où il a été opéré au dos ce mois-ci, selon l'agence de presse saoudienne. 

(c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2010 / Agence de presse saoudienne 

RYAD (Reuters) - Le roi Abdallah d'Arabie saoudite a quitté en bonne santé l'hôpital de New York où il a été opéré au dos ce mois-ci, a rapporté mercredi l'agence de presse saoudienne. 

"Le roi Abdallah a quitté l'Hôpital presbytérien mardi soir (...) car Dieu l'a doté d'une bonne santé", écrit l'agence saoudienne de presse. 

"Il s'est rendu à son lieu de résidence à New York pour récupérer et poursuivre ses soins", poursuit le communiqué, sans préciser la date de son éventuel retour en Arabie saoudite. 

Le roi Abdallah, qui aurait 86 ou 87 ans, a subi une deuxième intervention chirurgicale au dos destinée à stabiliser une vertèbre. 

Le prince Sultan, dont la santé est aussi fragile, est revenu en Arabie saoudite, premier exportateur mondial de pétrole, en l'absence du roi. 

Ulf Laessing, Bertrand Boucey pour le service français 

(c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2010]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761821&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.paris-normandie.fr/article/france-monde/le-roi-saoudien-aurait-quitte-lhopital-en-bonne-sante</original_link>
	<source>Paris-Normandie</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.paris-normandie.fr</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860553981</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>4</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>FRANCE</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XTSE">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XNYS">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XPAR">
	    <name>SES S.A.</name>
	    <symbol>SESG</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XLUX">
	    <name>SES S.A.</name>
	    <symbol>28734</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="4" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Arabie saoudite</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="SA" iso_code="SA" confidence="0.789348006248474">Saudi Arabia</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Mideast</region>
	    <latitude>25</latitude>
	    <longitude>45</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="3" confidence="0.951481997966766">
	    <location_name>New York</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US36" confidence="0.949032008647919">New York</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.949032008647919">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>40.7141990661621</latitude>
	    <longitude>-74.0064010620117</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761828">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Kamionba rohant egy kisteherautó - Egy halott]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Munkatársunktól]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Egy 53 éves férfi meghalt, a 66 éves érsekcsanádi sofőr pedig könnyebben sérült, amikor Iveco kisteherautójukkal egy szabályosan parkoló kamionba rohantak Kecelen szerda hajnalban. 

Szerda reggel negyed 5 körül, egy az út szélén szabályosan parkoló magyar kamionba rohant bele hátulról egy Iveco kistehergépkocsi Kecelen a Vadkerti úti 61. szám előtt. AZ Iveco Soltvadkert irányába közlekedett, amikor egyelőre nem tudni miért, de a kisteherautó az út szélén parkoló kamionba rohant. A gépkocsi vezetője, egy 66 éves érsekcsanádi férfi könnyebben sérült, azonban a kisteherautó utasa, egy 53 éves érsekcsanádi férfi a helyszínen életét vesztette.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761828&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221957</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>3</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761830">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Progesterone improves cognitive performance and attenuates smoking urges in abstinent smokers]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Sofuoglu M et al. – Progesterone, a steroid hormone, has been implicated in many CNS functions including reward, cognition, and neuroprotection. The goal of this study was to examine the dose–dependent effects of progesterone on cognitive performance, smoking urges, and smoking behavior in smokers. The findings suggest a potential therapeutic value of progesterone for smoking cessation.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761830&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.mdlinx.com/PsychLinx/xml-article.cfm/3405186</original_link>
	<source>MDLinx</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.mdlinx.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:02AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>14</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Industry'>
	    <category>Tobacco industry news</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>HealthCare</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Medical</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP35</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS62</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761831">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Turkish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[10:27 Necati: Hagi ile konuştuk ama...]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Son Dakika Spor 

A A+- 

Antalyaspor'da son lig maçında attığı golle 100'ler kulübüne giren Necati Ateş, Galatasaray'da oynadığı dönemde teknik direktör olan Hagi'nin kendisine olan güvenini hiçbir zaman boşa çıkarmadığını söyledi.  

Radyospor'da Özgür Sancar'la Haber Özel Programı'na bağlanan Necati, Antalyaspor'un uygun bulması durumunda, Galatasaray'a dönmeyi arzu ettiğini belirterek, "Şu ana kadar bana gelmiş bir teklif yok; ama ben Galatasaray'a dönmeyi, tekrar takımımın formasını giymeyi arzu ederim. Galatasaray'da oynadığım dönemde Hagi'nin bana olan güvenini hiçbir zaman boşa çıkarmadım. Kendisine çok büyük bir sevgi ve saygım var. Sakatlığım nedeniyle Galatasaray Tesisleri'ne tedavi için gitmiştim. Orada Hagi ile maçlarla ilgili bir konuşma yaptık. Transferden bahsetmedik" dedi.  

Necati Ateş, ayrılık sürecinde yaşananların Galatasaray'a dönmesi önünde sorun oluşturmayacağını ifade ederek, "Galatasaray'dan ayrılırken, bir takım sıkıntılar yaşadım. Ama bunlar takıma dönmem konusunda sıkıntı oluşturmaz. Geçmiş geçmişte kaldı. Ayrılırken de yöneticilerimize çok teşekkür ettim. Benim Galatasaray'a hiç bir kırgınlığım olamaz; çünkü ben bir futbolcuyum; işim sahada futbol oynamak" diye konuştu. ]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761831&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.feedsportal.com/c/32727/f/510259/s/10d6211c/l/0Lspor0Bmilliyet0N0Btr0Cnecati0Ehagi0Eile0Ekonustuk0Eama0E0Cspor0Cspordetay0C220B120B20A10A0C13294860Cdefault0Bhtm/story01.htm</original_link>
	<source>Milliyet</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.feedsportal.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>5</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>TURKEY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761832">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA['Get over it': Siddle to Poms]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Australia pace bowler Peter Siddle branded England as sore losers on Wednesday, saying they were only complaining about sledging because they lost the Perth Test. 

Siddle also turned up the heat on James Anderson, challenging the mouthy England quick to prove his toughness by carrying a side-strain injury into the fourth Ashes Test starting on Sunday at the MCG. 

England batsman Matt Prior was furious during last week's third Test when he was bowled by Siddle and then the Australian gave him a verbal send-off. 

Prior appeared to gesture for Siddle to join him later on in the car park so they could sort it out man to man, although Prior has denied this in a British newspaper column. 

He said Siddle's comments had annoyed him and weren't necessary. 

Prior said Siddle had got him out in "lucky" fashion and should have shut his mouth. 

"There are not many boxing matches when a guy knocks someone out and then kicks him while he's on the floor," Prior wrote in his column in The Independent newspaper. 

However Siddle said Prior had indeed asked him out the back for a fight and before he could respond, several of his team-mates had put up their hands. 

"Yeah I think he did (suggest having a fight) in the end," Siddle told a Cricket Victoria luncheon on Wednesday. 

Asked if he would have handled himself okay, the strongly built former junior wood-chopper grinned: "I'd back myself in."- aap 

Image by aap]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761832&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.sport927.com.au/news/cricket/get-over-it-siddle-to-poms</original_link>
	<source>Radio Sport 927</source>
	<source_category>Organisation</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.sport927.com.au</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860429664</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>AUSTRALIA AND NEW ZEALAND</subregion>
	  <country>AUSTRALIA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Sports'>
	    <category>Sports: cricket news</category>
	    <category>Sports: latest</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
	  <keyword>Sports</keyword>
	  <keyword>Cricket</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Poms</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="FR50" confidence="0.626797020435333"></province>
	    <country fips_code="FR" iso_code="FR" confidence="0.626797020435333">France</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>44.3405990600586</latitude>
	    <longitude>-1.00768995285034</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999956011772156">
	    <location_name>Australia</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="AS" iso_code="AU" confidence="0.608475029468536">Australia</country>
	    <subregion>Australia And New Zealand</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>-25</latitude>
	    <longitude>135</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="part of country" class="Administrative region" mentions="3" confidence="0.990483999252319">
	    <location_name>England</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="UK" iso_code="GB" confidence="0.904623985290527">United Kingdom</country>
	    <subregion>Northern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>53</latitude>
	    <longitude>-2</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.992735981941223">
	    <location_name>Perth</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="AS08" confidence="0.27351701259613">Western Australia State</province>
	    <country fips_code="AS" iso_code="AU" confidence="0.27351701259613">Australia</country>
	    <subregion>Australia And New Zealand</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>-31.9521999359131</latitude>
	    <longitude>115.861000061035</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.505863010883331">
	    <location_name>Victoria</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="CA02" confidence="0.403201013803482">British Columbia</province>
	    <country fips_code="CA" iso_code="CA" confidence="0.403201013803482">Canada</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>48.4333000183105</latitude>
	    <longitude>-123.349998474121</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">Siddle's comments had annoyed him and weren't necessary</property>
                <property name="person">Matt Prior</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">Prior had indeed asked him out the back for a fight and before he could respond, several of his team-mates had put up their hands</property>
                <property name="person">Peter Siddle</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">bowler</property>
                <property name="person">Peter Siddle</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">this in a British newspaper column</property>
                <property name="person">Matt Prior</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">Yeah I think he did (suggest having a fight) in the end</property>
                <property name="person">Peter Siddle</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Peter Siddle</property>
                <property name="instances">18</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.857</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">Victoria</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.087</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Matt Prior</property>
                <property name="instances">10</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.700</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">side-strain injury</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.316</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">United Kingdom</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.526</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Movie</property>
                <property name="value">Get over it</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.324</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">IndustryTerm</property>
                <property name="value">car park</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.261</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">bowler</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.324</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761839">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[娘にバレました。口止めした方がいいでしょうか？ - いやいや]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[保育園の年長組の娘に我が家のサンタの正体がバレました。どうやら昨年のクリスマスの頃から娘はサンタのことに薄々気付いていたそうで、先日とうとう娘から「パパでしょ」とハッキリ言われてしまいました。 

いつかは娘も真実を知ることになるだろうと思っていましたが、予想外に早かったです。すでに「パパ、クリスマスにはあのゲーム買って」と娘からリクエストされました。 

さて、ここで皆さんのご意見を参考にしたいのですが、娘がサンタの真実を保育園などで口外しないように口止めするべきでしょうか？ 

ユーザーID：0123161148 

お気に入り登録数：0 

古いレス順 

レス数：13本 

タイトル 

投稿者 

鈴とそり 

2010年12月22日 9:47 

私は幼児から小学生までと接する仕事をしています。 

小学生でも第一子なら高学年までサンタの存在を信じている子も結構います。 

みんながいる中で一人が「ほんとはサンタはおとうさんだ！」とか言うと、さっと空気が変わり騒然となることもあります。ほんと一瞬で楽しいサンタの存在が消えちゃうんです。 

サンタに対する考え方は各家庭それぞれですが、“真実を知るのはできるだけ後に延ばしたい”という親が多いと思います。 

小学生ならまだしも保育園児…もうちょっとよそのお子さんの夢を壊さないでもらえないですか？ 

保育園などで口外しないよう口止めということはもうすでに、 

「サンタはどこの家庭もみんなお父さんお母さんだ」とまで暴露してしまったのですか？ 

たとえ、トピ主さんの御家庭内でバレかけたとしても、私ならシラを切るかな。 

「今年はサンタさんが来れないと連絡があったので、パパが代わりになろうと思ってた」とか「うちはもうサンタさんじゃなくてお父さんがプレゼントしたくなった」とか、「今年限定」「我が家限定」としていくらでもまだ言い逃れはできたんじゃないですか。 

今からじゃ遅いですか？ 

ユーザーID：2573980204 

みゅう 

2010年12月22日 9:59 

もちろん口止めします。 

それからとぼけます。 

我が家も学校のお友達に、本当は親だと聞いてきました。 

娘はずっと信じていたようだったので、余計なことを…と憤りを感じましたが、 

「○○ちゃんのおうちは、お父さんが代役をサンタさんに頼まれたんだよ。世の中には子供達が沢山いるから、サンタさんの手が回らないときは、代わりにお願いしますっていうお便りが来るらしいよ。うちはまだ、お便りが来てないみたいだけど。」 

と言っておきました。 

信じているのかどうかは微妙な感じではありますが(汗)。 

『サンタさんに見えるように、紙に書いて貼っておかないと、ほしいもの置いて行ってくれないよ』と、昔から教え、その紙は見ているけど見ていない振り…お母さんはサンタさんに何をお願いしているのか知らないよ〜というスタンスを続けてきました。 

今年も紙に書いて、部屋の壁に貼っているので、信じてくれているのかなぁと思っています。 

もう１０歳なので、もういいのかもしれないとも思い、できる限り信じさせて夢を持たせてやりたいとも思い…、親心も複雑になってきました(笑)。]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761839&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/a138f19e621dfba60949c05ee0bcfbed?ul=MesJVx8a3c6TDDTKjjxDPA8sPSx0B2modyZTXSUtE3YEjl5KXuuh.ORtAYcwtnBP_GkUGPO3cBlvy0Zcf4DwegwvtIo_</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>13</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761840">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[DIARY - Turkey - to Jan 25, 2010]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[(All times are provisional and in GMT. For local time, add two 

hours. This diary is updated every day, and new listings or 

amendments are marked '*'.) 

KEY INDICATORS 

DATE GMT/LOCAL INDICATOR PERIOD PRIOR 

22/12 1430/1630 CPI forecast 2wk 8.10% 

23/12 0900/1100 Foreign arrivals Nov +8.52% 

28/12 1430/1630 Capacity utilisation Dec 75.9% 

28/12 1430/1630 Manufacturing conf Dec 107.6p 

30/12 0800/1000 Trade balance Nov -$6.33b 

3/1 N/A TIM export figures Dec $9.45b 

3/1 0800/1000 CPI m/m Dec 0.03% 

3/1 0800/1000 CPI y/y Dec 7.29% 

3/1 0800/1000 PPI m/m Dec 0.31% 

3/1 0800/1000 PPI y/y Dec +8.17% 

5/1 1430/1630 CPI forecast 2wk N/A 

10/1 0800/1000 Industrial Production Nov +9.8% 

11/1 1500/1700 Treasury cash balance Dec +5.79b 

11/1 0800/1000 Current account Nov 3.68b 

31/3 0800/1000 GDP Q4 5.5% 

17/1 0800/1000 Unemployment Oct 11.3% 

11/1 0900/1100 Budget balance Dec -365m 

17/1 0800/1000 Consumer confidence Dec 91.34 

13-20/1 1700/1900 Interest rate decision Jan 6.5% 

17-22/1 1500/1700 Govt debt stock Dec 465.5b 

WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 22 

ISTANBUL - Leaders from Iran, Pakistan, Afghanistan and 

Central Asia meet President Abdullah Gul and Prime Minister 

Tayyip Erdogan ahead of economic summit. 

ANKARA - Thai Foreign Minister Kasit Piromya meets Turkish 

counterpart Ahmet Davutoglu, Trade Minsiter Zafer Caglayan and 

business leaders. Until Dec 25. 

ISTANBUL - Economy Minister Ali Babacan to meet head of 49 

banks operating in Turkey. 

TOKYO - Energy Minister Taner Yildiz travels to Japan to 

hold talks on building nuclear-power plant. 

THURSDAY, DECEMBER 23 

ISTANBUL - Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad, Afghan 

President Hamid Karzai and Pakistani President Asif Ali Zardari, 

attend summit of Economic Cooperation Organisation (ECO) hosted 

by Turkey. 

Leaders from six Central Asian states also attending and 

Iraqi President Jalal Talabani is participating as an observer. 

FRIDAY, DECEMBER 24 

ISTANBUL - Gul to host fifth trilateral meeting between 

Turkey, Afghanistan and Pakistan. Afghan President Hamdi Karzai 

and Pakistani President Asif Ali Zardari attending. 

SUNDAY, DECEMBER 26 

ISTANBUL - Mavi Marmara, ship used in aid convoy to Gaza 

that ended in deadly Israeli raid in May, to return to Istanbul 

after repairs. 

MONDAY, DECEMBER 28 

SILIVRI, Turkey - Next hearing in so-called Sledgehammer 

trial of retired and active-duty military officers accused of 

plotting coup in 2003. 

TUESDAY, DECEMBER 29 

ANKARA - National Security Council meeting. 

WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 30 

*DIYARBAKIR, Turkey - Gul visits mainly Kurdish southeast's 

biggest city to meet with mayor, governor and civic groups. 

Until Dec 31. 

SATURDAY, JANUARY 1 

ISTANBUL - Istanbul Chamber of Commerce to release December 

inflation data for Turkey's biggest city. 

THURSDAY, JANUARY 13 

DIYARBAKIR, Turkey - Next hearing in trial of 151 Kurdish 

politicians and activists accused of links to outlawed Kurdistan 

Workers Party. 

SATURDAY, JANUARY 15 

ISTANBUL - Opening ceremony to be held for Turk Telekom 

Arena, new home of soccer club Galatasaray. Erdogan expected to 

attend (1700). 

MONDAY, JANUARY 24 

ISTANBUL - Next round of talks between Iran and Russia, 

United States, China, Britain, France and Germany on its nuclear 

programme expected to begin this week. 

TUESDAY, JANUARY 25 

GENEVA - Turkish and Greek Cypriot leaders attend tripartite 

summit with U.N. Secretary General Ban Ki-moon. Until Jan 26. 

ISTANBUL - Regional Mining Metals and Minerals Summit. 

NOTE - The inclusion of diary items does not necessarily 

mean Reuters will file a story based on the event. For the 

Reuters index of All Available Diaries, please click inside the 

brackets:. 

Keywords: DIARY TURKEY/ 

(Istanbul newsroom tel +90 212 350 7122; email: istanbul.newsroom@reuters.com)

COPYRIGHT

Copyright Thomson Reuters 2010. All rights reserved.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761840&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.finanznachrichten.de/nachrichten-2010-12/18905460-diary-turkey-to-jan-25-2010-020.htm</original_link>
	<source>FinanzNachrichten.de</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.finanznachrichten.de</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:01AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>20</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>GERMANY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Finance'>
	    <category>Finance latest</category>
            </channel>
            <channel name = 'Regional'>
	    <category>Afghanistan news</category>
	    <category>Turkey news</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Financials</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Wires</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP40</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS52</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XTSE">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XNYS">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="5" confidence="0.998385012149811">
	    <location_name>Turkey</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.964060008525848">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>39</latitude>
	    <longitude>35</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="9" confidence="0.948866009712219">
	    <location_name>ISTANBUL</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU34" confidence="0.918537974357605">Istanbul Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.918537974357605">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>41.0186004638672</latitude>
	    <longitude>28.9647006988525</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="2" confidence="0.998099029064178">
	    <location_name>Iran</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="IR" iso_code="IR" confidence="0.993866980075836">Iran (islamic Republic Of)</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>32</latitude>
	    <longitude>53</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="2" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Pakistan</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="PK" iso_code="PK" confidence="0.982033014297485">Pakistan</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>30</latitude>
	    <longitude>70</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="2" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Afghanistan</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="AF" iso_code="AF" confidence="0.993534028530121">Afghanistan</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>33</latitude>
	    <longitude>66</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="0.964044988155365">
	    <location_name>ANKARA</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU68" confidence="0.956974029541016">Ankara Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.956974029541016">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>39.9272003173828</latitude>
	    <longitude>32.8643989562988</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.865612983703613">
	    <location_name>Zafer</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.409197986125946">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>41.4500007629395</latitude>
	    <longitude>32.5666999816895</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.637524008750916">
	    <location_name>Caglayan</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU68" confidence="0.604303002357483">Ankara Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.604303002357483">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>39.9301986694336</latitude>
	    <longitude>32.907600402832</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.962840974330902">
	    <location_name>TOKYO</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="JA40" confidence="0.835295021533966">T?ky? Prefecture</province>
	    <country fips_code="JA" iso_code="JP" confidence="0.835295021533966">Japan</country>
	    <subregion>Eastern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>35.685001373291</latitude>
	    <longitude>139.751007080078</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999956011772156">
	    <location_name>Japan</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="JA" iso_code="JP" confidence="0.983887016773224">Japan</country>
	    <subregion>Eastern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>36</latitude>
	    <longitude>138</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="3" confidence="0.972149014472961">
	    <location_name>Istanbul</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU34" confidence="0.970196008682251">Istanbul Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.970196008682251">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>41.0186004638672</latitude>
	    <longitude>28.9647006988525</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>SILIVRI, Turkey</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU34" confidence="0.994947016239166">Istanbul Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.994947016239166">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>41.0764007568359</latitude>
	    <longitude>28.25830078125</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>DIYARBAKIR, Turkey</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU21" confidence="0.943953990936279">Diyarbak?r Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.943953990936279">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>37.9157981872559</latitude>
	    <longitude>40.2188987731934</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999001979827881">
	    <location_name>Russia</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="RS" iso_code="RU" confidence="0.990514993667603">Russia</country>
	    <subregion>Eastern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>60</latitude>
	    <longitude>100</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>United States</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.927594006061554">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>40</latitude>
	    <longitude>-100</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999791979789734">
	    <location_name>China</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="CH" iso_code="CN" confidence="0.956403970718384">China</country>
	    <subregion>Eastern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>36.5632019042969</latitude>
	    <longitude>103.832000732422</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.996322989463806">
	    <location_name>Britain</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="UK" iso_code="GB" confidence="0.968200981616974">United Kingdom</country>
	    <subregion>Northern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>52</latitude>
	    <longitude>0</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999756991863251">
	    <location_name>France</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="FR" iso_code="FR" confidence="0.95925498008728">France</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>46</latitude>
	    <longitude>2</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.997619986534119">
	    <location_name>Germany</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="GM" iso_code="DE" confidence="0.993909001350403">Germany</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>51</latitude>
	    <longitude>7</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.791747987270355">
	    <location_name>GENEVA</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SZ07" confidence="0.541929006576538">Geneva</province>
	    <country fips_code="SZ" iso_code="CH" confidence="0.541929006576538">Switzerland</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>46.2000007629395</latitude>
	    <longitude>6.16666984558105</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Reuters</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="GM05" confidence="0.267527997493744">Western</province>
	    <country fips_code="GM" iso_code="DE" confidence="0.267527997493744">Germany</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>50.6833000183105</latitude>
	    <longitude>9.36666965484619</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.996321976184845">
	    <location_name>TURKEY</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.949137985706329">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>39</latitude>
	    <longitude>35</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.91034197807312">
	    <location_name>istanbul</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="TU34" confidence="0.603130996227264">Istanbul Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="TU" iso_code="TR" confidence="0.603130996227264">Turkey</country>
	    <subregion>Western Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>41.0186004638672</latitude>
	    <longitude>28.9647006988525</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Economy Minister</property>
                <property name="person">Ali Babacan</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">President</property>
                <property name="person">Hamdi Karzai</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Afghanistan</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Prime Minister</property>
                <property name="person">Tayyip Erdogan</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Secretary General</property>
                <property name="person">Ban Ki-moon</property>
                <property name="organization">United Nations</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">President</property>
                <property name="person">Jalal Talabani</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Iraq</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCommunication</property>
                <property name="status">announced</property>
                <property name="person">Tayyip Erdogan</property>
                <property name="person">Ban Ki-moon</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCommunication</property>
                <property name="status">announced</property>
                <property name="person">Kasit Piromya</property>
                <property name="person">Ahmet Davutoglu</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Energy Minister</property>
                <property name="person">Taner Yildiz</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Foreign Minister</property>
                <property name="person">Kasit Piromya</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Thailand</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">President</property>
                <property name="person">Asif Ali Zardari</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Pakistan</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">President</property>
                <property name="person">Mahmoud Ahmadinejad</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Islamic Republic of Iran</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonTravel</property>
                <property name="status">future</property>
                <property name="locationdestination">Japan</property>
                <property name="person">Taner Yildiz</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">President</property>
                <property name="person">Hamid Karzai</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="country">Afghanistan</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonTravel</property>
                <property name="status">future</property>
                <property name="locationdestination">ISTANBUL</property>
                <property name="datestring">in May</property>
                <property name="date">2009-05-00</property>
                <property name="person">Asif Ali Zardari</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Central Asia meet President</property>
                <property name="person">Abdullah Gul</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">TOKYO</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Abdullah Gul</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.505</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Germany</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Currency</property>
                <property name="value">pence</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.311</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Islamic Republic of Iran</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.578</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">GENEVA</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">Turk Telekom Arena</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.125</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">DIYARBAKIR</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.195</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Currency</property>
                <property name="value">USD</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.323</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Region</property>
                <property name="value">Central Asia</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.287</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Prime Minister</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.287</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Ahmet Davutoglu</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.268</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Turkey</property>
                <property name="instances">8</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.667</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Ban Ki-moon</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Jalal Talabani</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.196</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Asia meet President</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.287</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">France</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Mahmoud Ahmadinejad</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">mayor , governor</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.147</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Japan</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">ISTANBUL</property>
                <property name="instances">11</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.694</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">President</property>
                <property name="instances">6</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.400</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Russia</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">United Nations</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Pakistan</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.510</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Asif Ali Zardari</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.245</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">United States</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Britain</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Afghanistan</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.510</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Energy Minister</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">Gaza</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.171</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Kasit Piromya</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.268</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">National Security Council</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.171</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Economy Minister</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.246</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Foreign Minister</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.268</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Taner Yildiz</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">ANKARA</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.323</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Istanbul Chamber of Commerce</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.125</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Hamdi Karzai</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.171</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">China</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Economic Cooperation Organisation</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.225</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Hamid Karzai</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.221</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Tayyip Erdogan</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.433</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Secretary General</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.105</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">head</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.246</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">PhoneNumber</property>
                <property name="value">+90 212 350 7122</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.053</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Company</property>
                <property name="value">Reuters</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.086</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">SILIVRI</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.171</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">EmailAddress</property>
                <property name="value">istanbul.newsroom@reuters.com</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.053</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">club Galatasaray</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.125</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Ali Babacan</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.246</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Workers Party</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.125</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Iraq</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.196</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">Thailand</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.268</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Central Asia meet President</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.287</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761844">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Spanish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[La operación Mercamadrid, protagonista del último pleno del año]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[El pleno extraordinario aprobará los presupuestos municipales de 2011, que se reducen un 8,9% hasta los 4.526,2 millones 

MADRID, 22 Dic. (EUROPA PRESS) - 

El Ayuntamiento de Madrid aprobará dedicar una calle al cantaor granadino Enrique Morente e informará sobre la operación de traspaso del usufructo de las acciones municipales de Mercamadrid a Madrid Espacios y Congresos durante el último Pleno del año, que se celebrará este miércoles en la Casa de la Villa.

La sesión de diciembre será escueta, a la vista del orden del día, dado que coincide con el Pleno extraordinario para la presentación y aprobación de los presupuestos del próximo ejercicio.

Así, los concejales aprobarán, previsiblemente por unanimidad, la propuesta del alcalde, Alberto Ruiz-Gallardón, de dedicar una calle o espacio público de la ciudad al cantaor granadino Enrique Morente, fallecido el pasado 13 de diciembre en la capital.

Por otra parte, el delegado de Hacienda, Juan Bravo, informará a la Corporación sobre la operación de traspaso del usufructo del 51 por ciento de acciones de Mercamadrid que posee el Ayuntamiento a la empresa pública Madrid Espacios y Congresos, movimiento que permitirá a las arcas municipales ingresar 187,7 millones de euros para agilizar los plazos de pago a proveedores.

Asimismo, se aprobarán las ordenanzas de Mercados Municipales y de Fomento del Asociacionismo y la Participación Ciudadana, y el delegado de Economía, Empleo y Participación Ciudadana, Miguel Ángel Villanueva, informará sobre las medidas para luchar contra el desempleo que ha puesto en marcha el Consistorio.

PRIVATIZACIONES

Por parte de la oposición, el presidente del Grupo Municipal Socialista, Óscar Iglesias, preguntará al Ejecutivo acerca del proceso de privatización del polideportivo de Chamartín, e instará al Pleno a "mostrar su rechazo y oposición" a este proceso.

IU ya ha adelantado que votará a favor de esta proposición aunque tampoco se dejará en el tintero las críticas al PSOE al tachar de "lamentable", en palabras del portavoz de IU en el Ayuntamiento, Ángel Pérez, que el Gobierno de la Nación recurra a la privatización de AENA y de la Lotería Nacional. "Que el Partido Socialista pretenda defender otro tipo de posiciones en el Ayuntamiento adolece de cierta falsedad en sus posiciones", añadió.

Para cerrar la sesión ordinaria, el edil de IU Daniel Morcillo preguntará sobre el cese de personal interino y las medidas a adoptar a partir de enero sobre los aspirantes que han superado las pruebas selectivas de auxiliares administrativos.

PLENO DE PRESUPUESTOS

Por otra parte, el Pleno municipal aprobará las cuentas preparadas por Juan Bravo para el próximo ejercicio, un proyecto que prevé una caída del 8,9 por ciento hasta los 4.526,2 millones de euros, una cifra equivalente a la que el Ayuntamiento manejaba hace un lustro.

Así, el titular de Hacienda defenderá ante la Corporación municipal unos presupuestos que contemplan caídas en todas las partidas y áreas de Gobierno, con especial incidencia en las inversiones reales, que perderán el 39,18 por ciento de su asignación, con lo que se concluirán los proyectos ya iniciados pero no se comenzará ninguno nuevo.

Esta situación se debe, además de a la crisis económica, a diferentes medidas como la decisión del Ejecutivo central de no permitir al Ayuntamiento refinanciar la deuda que vence en 2011, a la finalización del Plan E y a la congelación de los impuestos y tasas en la capital, según señala Bravo.

En cualquier caso, los responsables municipales han defendido desde la presentación del proyecto de presupuestos que los recortes no afectarán a los servicios sociales.

Sin embargo, para la oposición estas cuentas no cumplen los requisitos mínimos para atender las necesidades de la sociedad madrileña, razón que ha llevado a PSOE e IU a presentar sendas enmiendas a la totalidad, además de casi 400 enmiendas parciales tanto a los presupuestos como a las ordenanzas fiscales.

Así, IU defenderá una enmienda a la totalidad a la propuesta presentada por el PP, con 615 millones de euros más de ingresos y 433 menos de gastos mediante una modulación del IBI y la implantación en el capítulo de ingresos de nuevas tasas, como la turística, y la moratoria del pago a Madrid Calle 30 y el uso de patrimonio inmobiliario propio en el de gastos.

El PSOE, por su parte, presentará una enmienda a la totalidad por ser unas cuentas que mantienen "el despilfarro y los altos cargos por doquier" mientras que defenderán la creación de una Cuenta del Contribuyente para "acumular y fraccionar trimestralmente los recibos" de los impuestos municipales con el fin de dar facilidades a los contribuyentes para pagarlos.

No obstante, como ya sucedió en la última comisión de Hacienda, la mayoría absoluta del PP permitirá al Ejecutivo local aprobar sus cuentas sin necesidad de contar con la oposición, al igual que rechazar todas las propuestas de PSOE e IU.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761844&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.europapress.es/madrid/noticia-ayuntamiento-aprobara-dedicar-calle-morente-informara-operacion-mercamadrid-ultimo-pleno-ano-20101222055428.html</original_link>
	<source>Europa Press</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.europapress.es</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>4</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>SPAIN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="unknown" class="Spot feature" mentions="2" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Mercamadrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.74073600769043">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.74073600769043">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.3618011474609</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.65950989723206</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.99363100528717">
	    <location_name>MADRID</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.991715013980865">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.991715013980865">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4000015258789</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.68333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="4" confidence="0.976724982261658">
	    <location_name>Madrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.973558008670807">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.973558008670807">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4000015258789</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.68333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="unknown" class="Spot feature" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Casa de la Villa</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.994997978210449">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.994997978210449">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4178009033203</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.7022500038147</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="section of populated place" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.713136970996857">
	    <location_name>Chamartn</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.63809198141098">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.63809198141098">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4500007629395</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.70000004768372</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761845">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[妻の育児を見て - よみがえる記憶]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[妻は時短で働きながら育児をしています。 

遊ぶ時に色々工夫して物のやりとりで名前や色や数を教えたり、散歩中も危険や迷惑でなければ草木等触らせたりしています。 

私の母は専業主婦でしたが妻のように相手されてはいなかった気がします。 

外で触るのは汚いからダメ、服を汚すのも嫌がられた記憶があり、我が子に対しても小さいからわからない扱いです。 

母には月一程度会いますが子が色々知っているのを見て、保育園行くと教えなくても覚えて来ると感心しています。 

叱る時も妻は子供が知らずにした事は一切怒らず何故いけないか説明し、わざとしたら厳しく叱ります。 

何故子供がそんな事をしたかも良く察します。 

そのせいか親バカですが一歳前でも親の言う事が驚く程わかっていました。 

少しずつ注意の声や顔を厳しくするので大抵キツく叱る前に子供もやめます。 

私の子供時代は親を怒らせる事をすると叱られたものです。 

親の機嫌に寄る事も多々ありました。 

私の親も決して悪い親ではなかったと思いますし感謝もしていますが、上記以外にも色々あり妻に育てられる子供は幸せだなと思っています。 

そういう人いませんか？ 

ユーザーID：5492775975 

お気に入り登録数：109 

古いレス順 

レス数：32本 

1 2   すべて トピ主のみ(1) 

タイトル 

投稿者 

なな 

2010年12月19日 15:16 

世の中の子育て中のママが、トピ主さんの奥様の 

ような方だったら、どんなにいいか・・・。 

私もそういうママになりたいと思います！ 

ユーザーID：1328583929 

nana 

2010年12月19日 15:57 

私も奥様のような育児をしています 

子供はすごく素直で育てやすいです。 

危ないことや人にいじわるもしないのでとても私が楽です 

病気もほとんどなし 

私は主さま母と同じようなお母さんに育てられたので、反面教師でした。 

小さくても何でも教えました 

耳で聞くことも大切にし、本物の楽器の音を（ホテルなどでやる生演奏のオーケストラなど）聞きにいったり 

食事も外でよくします（テーブルマナー的なこと） 

今３歳と５歳ですが 

特に塾などにもいかせてないですが 

上の子は５〜7歳対象の全国的模試で（幼稚園で実施されたもの）教育熱心な１００人中年中ながら１位でした 

下の子は３歳半ですが、年長の子と同じように計算ができたり、本も一人で読みます 

園の先生のほとんどに入園当初から、聞き分けがよく本当に３歳かと驚かれていました 

何でも実体験させます 

私は小さいころから「まだ分からないだろう」と母は思って教えないで自然に来たため、後になって苦労がありました 

ゆとりのある親の対応は子供にもいい影響で 

好きなようにさせながらも、少しヒントを与えながらしています 

ユーザーID：2844110431 

ムービー 

2010年12月19日 16:02 

奥様にその気持ち伝えてくださいね。 

ユーザーID：9873402530 

nana 

2010年12月19日 16:02 

今は育児書など多種多様色んないい本が出ているので、育児もお母さんによって様々でしょうが 

いい育児を目指している方は多いと思います。 

３歳精神を私は信じてとにかく３歳までは色んなことをさせましたが 

結局４歳になっても５歳になっても好奇心を大切にしていると何でも見てやらせ体験させ失敗もさせる。 

親がニコニコで温かい気持ちで接していると子供も素直でニコニコの子になると思います 

私は教育熱心にはなりたくないので、子供を常に尊重し 

間違った方向にいかないようにだけ見ていますが、やりたいことはやらせ、その子の向き不向きはすごく分かっているつもりです 

こうやって親が子供に目を向けて（必要以上の口は出さないで自尊心を大切に）していると 

子供もすごくまっすぐ応えてくれて相乗効果でお互いが気持ちよく 

手もかからずに子供も自分でできるようになり嬉しいです 

押さえつけてると、大きくなってから反発が出たり曲がっていったりするんじゃないかと思います 

ユーザーID：2844110431 

抹茶味 

2010年12月19日 16:48 

トピ主さんの奥様は上手に子育てなさっているようですね。 

すごく素敵な女性なんだろうなと想像できます。 

でもトピ主さんが育児に協力的だったりして、奥様の育児に対するストレスが少ないんじゃないですか？ 

時短で働いているというところも、良いのかもしれませんね。 

私の知人も「専業主婦だった頃より、働き出して子供と少し離れるようになってからのほうが、子供が可愛く思える」と言っている人が何人か居ます。 

どんな親でも、どんな子育てのやりかたでも、親から愛されて育った子はそれだけでとても幸せだと思いますよ。 

ユーザーID：2631625431 

三線 

2010年12月19日 16:52 

働きながら、しっかり育児なさっている。きっと、感受性豊かで、躾の行き届いた良いお子さんに育つことでしょう。 

私の母は子ども嫌いです。だから、私が母にまとわり付くと振り払われました。外出しても自分のペースで歩く（しかもただでさえ通常の人より早足）ので、私は小走りに、時には走りながら付いて行きました。信号を渡り損ねたら、怒られました。 

そのため、私は大阪・東京辺りに行くと遅足ですが、住んでいる地域では「歩くの早すぎ」「三線を見かけたから一緒に行こうと思って追いかけたんだけど、追いつけなかった」と言われます。 

また、人に触られるのが大嫌い。いきなり触られると飛び上がるほどびっくりしてしまい、相手をびっくりさせてしまいます。 

カウンセラーや児童心理に詳しい知り合いに相談すると、「赤ちゃん時代や幼児期のスキンシップが足らなかったのかもね」と言われますが、今更どないせえ言うんじゃ、です。 

ユーザーID：5677904295 

みぃ 

2010年12月19日 16:59 

すごく素敵な奥さまですね！ 

私は現在第一子を妊娠中、８ヶ月ですが、是非奥さまのような子育てをしたいなと思いました！ 

素敵なトピをありがとうございました。 

ユーザーID：9087135405 

とうじょう　かおる 

2010年12月19日 18:04 

トピ主さんと同じようなことを、母から何度も何度も言われます。 

私の育児が素晴らしいと褒めてくれます。 

ですが、嬉しいというよりは、自身の子供時代を振り返って哀しくなります。 

父にはアルコール依存症で殴られ、母にはヒステリーで暴言を吐かれました。 

子供を産むまで、それが普通の育児だと思っていたし、親にも感謝していました。 

でも実際に育児をしてみると、イライラなんて大人として自分で消化できる。子供に当り散らすなんて有り得ない。頭ごなしに怒ることも不要。まさにトピ主さんの奥様のような育児は普通にできています。 

私が特に育てにくかったわけではありません。むしろ優等生でイイ子でした。両親も私たちも夫婦共働きですが、両親は母の親が近くにいて保育園の送迎などをしてくれました。私たちは夫婦だけで、足りない部分はファミサポなどを利用しています。 

母には今でも感謝していますが、どうしてこれくらいの普通の育児（感情的に当り散らさない）をしてくれなかったのか、とても哀しく思います。 

娘は、天真爛漫で子供らしく、悪いこともしますが諭せば分かります。幸せだったらいいなと思います。 

ユーザーID：6554384014 

華 

2010年12月19日 19:06 

トピ主さんと同じ事を前夫が言ってました。 

｢お前に育ててもらいたかった｣と。 

可哀想な育ちだったのと、息子が性格やおねしょ癖があることなど自分にそっくりだったため、余計羨ましかったようです。 

同じように育ててくれていたら、自分の未来は変わっていたんじゃないかと息子が羨ましいとよく言っていました。 

離婚しましたが、可哀想な人でした。 

ユーザーID：4874202635 

それはさ 

2010年12月19日 19:20 

良い意味で。 

もちろん絶対じゃないし、極端に片方だけがおかしい場合も 

あるでしょうが、夫婦は合わせ鏡というように 

影響しあってますからね。 

私も基本的に親には感謝してますが、母は四六時中文句を 

言ってるような神経質な人でした。子供に対してあたりがきつかったです。 

比べて父は寡黙だけど、母より尊敬できると思ってました。 

でも、大人になり、家を離れ客観的に考えるようになり 

父も退職して親夫婦のかたちが変わって行くのを見ていて 

ああ、そうかと。母が神経質だった原因の一端は 

寡黙で家庭の責任を母に丸投げしていた父にも 

あったんです。うちの親はどちらも悪ではない。 

でもお互い様だったんです。夫婦って、子供からも 

全貌は見えないものなんですね。 

ちなみに兄は私と正反対のアプローチで、同じ結論に 

達してました。私よりも親の若い頃を知っている分、 

父が悪くて母がああなんだと思っていたんですよ。 

でも今なら親父の気持ちもわかるなと。 

子育てって自分を育て直すようなものだと言うじゃないですか。 

奥様が良い子育てをなさってるのは、きっと貴方が 

良いお父さんだからだというのもあると思います。。 

ユーザーID：1567702978 

ニッキ 

2010年12月19日 20:05 

水を差すようですが、タイトルのとおりです。 

大人の言う事が徐々に理解できるようになってきて、言う事を聞くようになります。 

これが、徐々に２歳を過ぎてくると、嘘をつくことを覚えたり、自分の意思が強くなってきたりします。 

なので、真価は、２歳３歳以降でしょう。 

ちなみに、うちは２歳。 

同じように、頭ごなしにしかることはなく、よく言い聞かせていますので、魔の２歳ではありますが、そこまでひどくはないですが。 

それでも、親の言う事を聞かないときが出てくるようになりました。 

ユーザーID：5215290111 

はむ 

2010年12月19日 20:18 

奥様が余裕があって相手の立場にたって子育てが出来ているのは 

貴方という安心感と余裕があるからですよ。 

そして、余裕安心感を与えられる父親になったあなたは 

多少嫌な思いをしたとしても 

ちゃとした教育を受けて育った素敵な男性です。 

子供を思う気持ち 

親を思う気持ち 

色々交差しますね。 

その中で、貴方に今できる事を 

将来に繋がっていく事を冷静に考えながら 

この、短くも長い人生を、歩んで行こうではありませんか。 

素晴らしい事を一つでも見つけながら生きていくのが 

「生きる事」の意味でもあります 

ユーザーID：0261599753 

母 

2010年12月19日 21:59 

そして、それに気づいたムーミンパパさまも、すてきな方だなあと思います。 

きっとお子様、賢く明るい子に育つでしょうね。 

ムーミンパパ様もおっしゃるとおり、あなたのお母様も「悪い親ではない」と思います。多くのお母さんは、そんなものです。 

うちの母も機嫌が変わりやすく、私はいつも顔色を見てびくびくしていました。 

学校から帰ると母をそっと見て「今日は機嫌が悪いな」「やったー、機嫌がいい」 

悩み事を相談できる雰囲気ではありませんでした。 

汚したり、失敗すると、露骨に嫌な顔をされました。 

私は、自分の子を育てるとき（完璧ではないけど）気をつけました。 

３人とも、情緒の安定したおっとりした子に育ち、家の中は和やかで、弱音やグチも言えるし、笑顔や冗談の絶えない家です。 

祖父母や親の健康をきづかってくれ、部活やサークルで友達とも楽しそうにやっています。 

ムーミンパパさんのお子さんもたっぷり愛情を受け、優しい子になるでしょうね。 

奥さまとこのままずっと仲良くしてくださいね。 

ユーザーID：7230132370 

ラマ 

2010年12月20日 0:25 

本の手本のような教育方法です。 

幸せですよね、そんなお母さんに育てられる子は。 

私の祖母が奥さんのように、 

優しくて口はあまり出さず、手は出す（助けてくれる） 

孫の私には無償の愛で育ててくれました。 

そんな素敵な祖母に育てられた母は・・ 

自分の事だけを心配すれば良い人で 

子供の為に時間を割くのが出来ない人でした。 

そんな母に育てられた私達姉妹は 

平凡な主婦になりました。 

おばぁちゃんほどではありませんが、 

無償の愛を子供に注げる人間だと思っています。 

母のように育っていても、 

自分の事は自分で守る人なので、 

依存とかされないし（逆に幼稚園の時から子離れ 

してくれてるけど） 

やっぱり、人間、母のように自分を大事にする術も 

覚えないといけないし・・ 

そう思うと、母は良き人生の先生です。 

きっと、お母さんのおかげでトピさんは 

愛情深い人に育ったんですね。 

人に愛情をあげれる人になれたんです。 

だからそんな素敵な奥さんと結ばれたんですね。 

ユーザーID：9470141999 

アイ 

2010年12月20日 3:46 

理想的な子育てですね！ 

もっと色々、具体的に教えて欲しいです。 

そして、奥様がなさってきたことに対し、そういう風に評価のできるトピ主様も素敵ですね☆ 

私は実母よりは、絶対に良い母だと言えますが（笑）夫の義母に対しては頭が上がりません…私もいつか義母を超えられたら！ 

夫にそう思ってもらえるよう頑張ります。 

ユーザーID：8352509456 

忍びの者 

2010年12月20日 9:51 

そうそう、親はけっして悪い人ではなかったし、感謝もしていますが、腑に落ちないんですよね。 

子供の頃、親が怒った理由とか、推測できる立場になると、改めて失望というか、まぁ、がっかりしたりします。 

コレって、人間の進化かもしれませんね。 

親の子供時代って、社会から教育を受ける事ができていたように、想像しています。だから、常識とかマナーを、教わらなくても、ある程度は育っていたのだと思いますね。また、そういう世の中だったのだと思います。でもそのせいか、両親は親として、改めて教育する事ができていなかったと感じています。悪いとか、言えるようなものじゃなくて、社会の変化に対して旧態依然だったというか。 

私たちの世代では、子供には躾や教育をしないと社会が成り立たないと、教えられ始めていると思います。勿論、まだ気付いていない人もいますけど。。。 

そうやって、社会が進んでいくのでしょうね。 

大人として、良い世の中にしていきたいと、小さな子を見ると思います。 

ユーザーID：0500990632 

嫉妬？ 

2010年12月20日 11:15 

同じように育てています。 

でも４歳の娘は最近本当に手がかかります。 

２歳の子供もおりますが、こちらは本当にいい子ですが理解力はいまひとつ。（それがまたかわいいのだけど） 

我が子自慢のレスを見たりすると、なんだかもやもやしてしまいました。 

その子の個性による部分はかなりあると思います。 

ただトピ主さんがいいお父さんなのは間違いないです。 

家族みんなで尊敬しあえる素敵なご家庭なのだと思います。 

ユーザーID：2196370612 

け〜ちゃん 

2010年12月20日 14:55 

本当に申し訳ないですが、まだわからない…というのが私の経験からくる持論です。 

1歳？かわいかったですよ。こっちも余裕がありました。 

でも、今3歳前。もうだめです。嘘も覚え口ごたえも覚え、やることなす事幼いくせにイッチョマエです。 

1歳の時のように言い聞かせることが、格段に難しいです。 

今現在ウチの夫の口癖は「1歳の時が懐かしい」です。それくらいすごいです。 

先日、友人たちと一緒に忘年会がありました。 

そのなかの0歳児のお母さんが、ウチの娘に色々言ってました。（騒がないようにご飯の後にチョコを食べさせたりしてたのを子供に向かって「はずかしいよ〜0歳児チャンだって良い子にしてるよ〜」とか。何度も）でも、「そんな事言って、これはあなたの0歳児チャンが通る道よ？チョコでちゃんと座って良い子にしてるんだからこの子は躾が出来てるほうよ。2歳児の本当の恐ろしさを知らないのに嫌味を言わないことよ」と、他のお母さんがフォローしてくれたので溜飲を下げました。 

もちろん奥さんは間違ってないですが（むしろ素晴らしい！）、真価はこれからでしょうね。お父さんも頑張って下さい。 

ユーザーID：6526811060 

ひかり 

2010年12月20日 16:36 

私も「お姉ちゃんなんだから」「女なんだから」と言って育てられました。 

今ではあまりそういうことは言わないようにしようとなってますよね。 

弟も「長男なんだから」と甘やかされ、期待され育てられましたが、今では「長男教」と言われてますし、親元遠く離れてしまいました。 

私の母親が子供が成人した後 

「お隣さんから朝中学生の子供をしかり飛ばす声が聞こえてくるのよねー。私もあなたたちが中学生くらいの時にはそうだったのかしら？って思うわー」 

って言ってました。人のことだとわかるんですね。 

子育てしている時はいっぱいいっぱいだったのが、孫に対してだと一歩ひいて見れるんでしょうねー。 

でも親の機嫌で怒られるのも悪いことばかりではありませんよ。 

空気が読める人に育ちます。 

私は母親が誰かに怒ると他の全員に当たり散らすという性格だったので、家族全員大変空気が読める人間に育ちました。 

弟も男の割にはすごく空気が読めます。それは良かったのではないかと思います。 

ユーザーID：2541694031 

さくさく 

2010年12月20日 22:25 

私の母親はキャリアの先駆けで、当時は珍しい兼業主婦でした。 

経済的な理由ではなく、自分が家庭だけしか世界を持たないと、力が余り過ぎてダメな母親になる自信があったため、仕事を続けていたそうです。 

接する時間が限られていたから、感情的に怒りをぶつけられたり、理不尽な叱られ方をされた覚えは一切ありません。 

働く母は憧れであり、いつも笑顔でした。 

自然と、私も働く母になりました。主さんの奥様や実母と同じく、子供には丁寧に接することができていると思います。もちろん魔の２歳児も経験しましたし、上の子は下の子が生まれる前後では赤ちゃん返りも多少はありました。が、６歳と２歳の姉弟は、感情が安定していて、癇癪を起こしたことはありません。「ママは怒ったことがないねー」とくすくす笑われますが、一度言ったことはすぐ理解してくれるので、声を荒げる場面がないのです。接する時間が短いからこそ、楽しく穏やかに過ごすことができるのだと思います。 

専業主婦としての育児は、醜い自分も見せねばならない気がして、私には無理です。]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761845&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/0f199a680d52ad75752c4a6953ce38e1?ul=MVy95UHRKPDAWXgrAYT7AJH1NNPI6pUeJKI.LYYrOEyXZ8yrRqJ3j4gB_11moCWV0FQ1l92OS6piTqc4U0p2b3M8wiLM</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>15</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761849">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Korean">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[아스공항, “항공 수하물 파손 걱정하지 마세요”]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[STAYKIT]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[[뉴스핌=이연춘기자] 아스공항(대표 기옥)이 22일 인천국제공항의 수하물 적재 공정에 아시아 최초로 항공기 승객 수하물 적재 보조설비(Vacuum Baggage Lifter) 1대를 시범 도입해 운용한다고 밝혔다. 

일명 크레인 브리지(Crane Bridge)로 불리는 이 장비는 흡착식 방식을 통해 수하물을 컨테이너에 적재하는 것으로, 최대 45kg 중량의 수하물까지 작업할 수 있고 일일 최대 1000개 가량의 수하물 처리가 가능한 최첨단 장비이다. 

1대당 가격이 4200여 만원에 이르는 수하물 적재 보조설비는 영국의 히드로 공항을 비롯한 전 세계 주요 10여개 공항에서 운용되는 최신 설비로써, 아스공항은 내년부터 해당 설비를 단계적으로 추가 도입해 차별화된 서비스 제공은 물론 영업 경쟁력에서도 우위를 확보할 수 있을 것으로 기대하고 있다. 

아스공항 기옥 사장은 "수작업시 발생할 수 있는 승객 수하물의 파손을 원천적으로 차단하고, 해당 근로자들의 근골격계질환 발생 요인을 제거할 수 있어 해당 설비 도입을 결정했다"고 밝혔다. 

[뉴스핌 Newspim]이연춘 기자 (lyc@newspim.com)]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761849&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.newspim.com/view.jsp?newsId=20101222000188</original_link>
	<source>NewsPim</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.newspim.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>26</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>KOREA REPUBLIC OF</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Financials</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP40</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS52</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761852">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[学童保育の行事がとっても良いんです（カテ違いの自慢？） - 学童保育はとってもいいです]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761852&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/64fb5287334e4c89774fed7bb78d65ea?ul=ZEJMYKUMuQdIJEnN6qz8J8UnFI3Xx_xgekjp6Z7.yZCvVhfNga.z1QqbtbYdt4fZsuH9Nthw6JSElLdtA9bBD0mbJqDF</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>17</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761859">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Japanese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[実家依存症について - 世間知らず]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[はじめまして　アラフォー×１の「人間不信気味」です。 

タイトルどおり私は妻の「実家依存症」より離婚いたしました。 

離婚は調停にまで発展したのですが、私は「実家依存症」はいけないことと思っていましたが、調停の場では「価値観」で処理されてしまい全く話合いの議題になりませんでした。論点は「実家依存症」なのにです。 

世間の方々は「実家依存症」は人の「価値観」とお考えなのかと思い、 

トピを立てさせていただきました。 

よろしくお願いします。 

ユーザーID：0794343660 

お気に入り登録数：192 

古いレス順 

レス数：190本 

1 2 3 4 5   すべて トピ主のみ(17) 

タイトル 

投稿者 

ys-o 

2010年9月9日 11:52 

法に触れるわけでもないし、価値観と言われれば価値観なんでしょうね。 

＞「実家依存症」はいけないことと思っていましたが 

あなたはそう思うでしょうけど、ご主人が「べつにいいよ」と言う人だったら問題ないわけですし。 

まぁ、一般的には良くは思われないでしょうし、私も実家依存が強い人は好きではないですけどね。 

ユーザーID：8642254376 

老婆神 

2010年9月9日 12:14 

妻が実家依存症であることに対して、 

あなたが何を問題にしているのか、私には判らない。 

ユーザーID：7791797639 

syou 

2010年9月9日 12:23 

実家依存症は認知度低いです。それに、問題は実家依存症が夫婦関係にどんな被害をもたらしたかで、それを証明出来なければならないでしょう。 

価値観の問題で終始してしまったのは、上記を証明できなかったか、相手方のほうが上手だったのでしょうね 

ユーザーID：0275360568 

まるみ 

2010年9月9日 12:25 

タイトルの通り難しい問題ですね。 

結論からいうと私は｢価値観の違い｣だと思います。 

私は主人の母親・実家への依存で別れましたが｢価値観の違い｣で納得しています。 

ユーザーID：0174811412 

ローズ 

2010年9月9日 12:28 

うーん。私の友人、ほとんど実家依存かも。 

トピ主さんの基準がわかりませんが、結婚後、隣の市などに嫁いだ 

友人達も、実家ばかり戻ってきてましたよ。長期で泊まったり。 

同じ市内で結婚した友達も、毎日実親と過ごしています。 

ご主人も、快く承諾しているようで、お互いの親同士も仲良しです。 

子供が生まれてからは、ますます実家にいる日が多いです。 

しかも、金銭的な援助もしてもらってますが、ご主人も、 

『助かる、ありがとうございます』って感じで、別に気にしてない様子。 

お姑さんも、最近の方はご理解があるらしく、 

『やっぱり娘は実母が一番だものね。ゆっくりしておいで』って言って、 

お土産まで持たせてくれるそうです。 

価値観の違いってことは、両家の親に対する考え方の違いなのでは？ 

お嫁さんが実家にばかり行ってしまっても、上手くいってる家庭は 

結構あります。 

ユーザーID：2049933303 

おてて 

2010年9月9日 12:38 

程度によると思いますが調停の場ではソウ処理されたのですよね。 

そしてそれ以外の論点によって離婚成立したのですよね？ 

ユーザーID：4755148902 

リンコ 

2010年9月9日 12:55 

妻の実家依存で離婚！ 

ユーザーID：3794878176 

まる 

2010年9月9日 13:46 

＞私は「実家依存症」はいけないことと思っていましたが 

それが、価値観なのです。 

あなたにとってそれは「依存だ、いけない事だ」でも、他の方から見たら依存ではなく「嫁に言っても親を大切にする親孝行な娘」と取るかもしれません。だいたい、あなたのトピには別れた奥様がどんな風に実家に依存していたかも書かれていないので、本当に依存していたかもわかりませんし、別れた奥様の実家に対するあり方が「依存」と言うほどではなく、それこそ「価値観」の範囲内だったのかもしれません。 

それでもあなたが「いや、そんな事はない元妻のあれは実家依存症だ」と言うなら、第三者が公平な目で判断できるよう、どんな依存があったか書いていただけませんか？]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761859&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.rssad.jp/rss/artclk/1YlJkhzd5znB/131da3e7d06303152706a7596e12276a?ul=ovVEjv_xiipA19uYWMQcXr_3.C3pi6jkjsqZKfXww8x2dkNYsETsT.Q0KHCOl3a6Ddc8Y9S_8GMmYOP3VjYKPKHh9R4u</original_link>
	<source>Yomiuri Shimbun</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Yomiuri Shimbun</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.rssad.jp</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>20</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>JAPAN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761860">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Közzétett az új-zélandi hadsereg UFO-jelentéseket]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Független Hírügynökség]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Titkosított UFO-jelentéseket hozott nyilvánosságra szerdán az új-zélandi hadsereg az 1954 és 2009 közötti időszakról. 

Titkosított UFO-jelentéseket hozott nyilvánosságra szerdán az új-zélandi hadsereg az 1954 és 2009 közötti időszakról. Több ezer anyagot tettek közzé, és csak a neveket, a személyazonosításra alkalmas adatokat távolították el. 

A közemberek, katonák, és kereskedelmi gépek pilótáinak beszámolóiból közzétett csaknem kétezer dokumentum harmadik típusú találkozásokról, rejtélyes fényjelenségekről számol be. Több anyagban rajzok látható repülő csészealjakról, maszkokat viselő földönkívüliekről, és az állítólagos idegenek kézírásaiból vett mintákból. 

Az új-zélandi légierő illetékese, Kavae Tamariki azt mondta a Dominion Post nevű lapnak, hogy nem kívánják kommentálni az iratokat, amely igazságtartalmát nem vizsgálták, csupán az információs szabadságról szóló törvény szellemében jártak el a közzététellel. 

Az egyik legmeghökkentőbb, közzétett eset 1978-ban történt, amikor az új-zélandi tévé stábja egy repülőről véletlenül tanúja volt két fényjelenségnek, és az egyiket fel is vették a déli sziget, Kaikoura térségében. A felvétel nemzetközi médiaszenzáció volt. A légierő utóbb azt állította, hogy a felhőkről verődtek vissza hajók fényei vagy a Vénusz fénye jelent meg különös visszaverődésként a felhőkön. 

A szerdán közzétett dokumentumok mellett további több ezer irat van még UFO-król. Azokat 2080-ig titkosították a nemzeti archívumban.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761860&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221954</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>4</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761873">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Norwegian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Nå har du sjansen til å fryse ut denne]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Har du barn med middallergi i huset, er det lurt å bruke kalde dager til å kvitte seg med en del av . Midd har vi alle i sengene våre, og for dem som er allergiske mot de små krypene kan det føre til tunge netter med tett nese og rennende øyne. Sett ut madrassen - Man dreper midden ved temperaturer under -15 grader, så det kan være lurt å sette ut madrasser når det er kaldt. Dyner og puter kan også gjerne henges ut, sier rådgiver Grethe Amdal i . Sett alt ut om morgenen, for det tar hele åtte timer å bli kvitt all midden. Husk også å banke madrassen og riste pute og dyne godt før du tar det inn. På denne måten får du fjernet mest mulig av midden og middavføringen. Spiser døde hudceller - Det viktigste er nok likevel å passe på at soverommet er så støvfritt som mulig. Vask sengetøy og kosedyr jevnlig på 60 grader, støvsug sengebunnen og madrassen godt og unngå støvsamlere som åpne kasser og hyller, sier Amdal. Også gardiner, tepper og sofaer er steder der støv og midd trives godt. Støvet i huset ditt består nemlig i stor grad av hudceller, og det er dette midden lever av. Ergo trives midden godt i selskap med hybelkaninene dine. Hold det tørt - Foreldre bør også passe på at luftfuktigheten i huset ikke blir for høy. Anbefalt luftfuktighet er 20-40 prosent, og blir fuktigheten høyere enn dette trives midden bedre. Sjekk inneklimaet og finn ut om det er god nok ventilasjon i boligen deres. Unngå også å henge opp klesvasken i rom dere oppholder dere, og hold døren til badet lukket når dere har dusjet. I tillegg til at fuktigheten gir gode levervilkår for midden, vil den også kunne føre til mugg i huset, sier Amdal. Verre andre steder Selv om midd er et stort problem for dem som er allergiske, er Norge tross alt et greit land å bo i for middallergikere. Særlig for dem som bor på innlandet. - Verst er det på vestlandet der vintrene er milde og fuktigere, men sammenligner man med for eksempel England er ikke midd et kjempeproblem her i landet, mener avdelingsdirektør Preben Ottesen i avdeling for skadedyrskontroll ved Folkehelseinstituttet. Ikke re sengen Ottesens anbefaling er å støvsuge senger, sofaer og tepper samt å skifte på sengen hver uke. Et annet tips som særlig de yngste nok setter pris på er å ikke re opp sengen om morgenen. Legg heller dynen til side slik at fuktigheten tørker opp. - Selv om det er middallergikere som plages av dette, skader det ikke at også resten av familien tenker gjennom vanene sine. Da er man ikke så utsatt for å utvikle allergi, sier Ottesen. Noen flere tips: Du kan legge dynen og puten i fryseren en dag og deretter riste det godt. Dette tar også livet av midden Det finnes middtrekk til madrass, dyne og pute. Disse forhindrer at midden kommer inn, og kan være til hjelp for dem som sliter med middallergi Bruk esker med lokk til oppbevaring på barnerommet. Velg også helst skap som går til taket Barn oppholder seg mye i sengen og på rommet. Vær derfor nøye med rengjøringen NAAF anbefaler rengjøring etter tørrprinsippet med tørrmopp, mikrofiberklut og støvsuger Dugg på vinduene er et tegn på at det er for mye fuktighet i boligen Ikke re opp sengen om morgenen. Legg dynen til side slik at fuktigheten slipper ut Kilde: Les også: Saken ble opprinnelig publisert på Klikk.no. Les her.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761873&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.dagbladet.no/2010/12/22/tema/klikk/helse/14812563/</original_link>
	<source>Dagbladet</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.dagbladet.no</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>2</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>NORWAY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Health</keyword>
	  <keyword>Lifestyle</keyword>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XTKS">
	    <name>O-M Ltd.</name>
	    <symbol>6213</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.816078007221222">
	    <location_name>Verre</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="BE07" confidence="0.346650004386902">Namur</province>
	    <country fips_code="BE" iso_code="BE" confidence="0.346650004386902">Belgium</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>50.2000007629395</latitude>
	    <longitude>5.05000019073486</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999971985816956">
	    <location_name>Norge</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="NO" iso_code="NO" confidence="0.343903988599777">Norway</country>
	    <subregion>Northern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>62</latitude>
	    <longitude>10</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Verst</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="DA21" confidence="0.498225003480911">Region Syddanmark</province>
	    <country fips_code="DA" iso_code="DK" confidence="0.498225003480911">Denmark</country>
	    <subregion>Northern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>55.5499992370605</latitude>
	    <longitude>9.25</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="part of country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.482903987169266">
	    <location_name>England</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="UK" iso_code="GB" confidence="0.482434004545212">United Kingdom</country>
	    <subregion>Northern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>53</latitude>
	    <longitude>-2</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761876">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Internacional re-signs coach Celso Roth for 2011]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[RIO DE JANEIRO, Dec. 21 (Xinhua) -- Despite Internacional's disappointing third place finish in the 2010 Club World Cup, the Brazilian team announced Tuesday to renew a contract with head coach Celso Roth through 2011.

Roth arrived at the Brazilian club in July after the dismissal of Uruguayan coach Jorge Fossati. He found immediate success after winning the 2010 Libertadores Cup, falling to the grace of the club's fans and administration.

However, after Internacional suffered the disappointing loss to TP Mazembe in the semifinals of the 2010 Club World Cup, Roth's job was placed into question.

He received the full support of vice president Fernando Carvalho who stated that he believes the coach will give continuity to the hard work developed and produced in 2010.

Roth is also gotten back by his players, who claimed that the coach is a great leader and extremely knowledgeable and a friend to all.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761876&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://english.sina.com/sports/2010/1221/353005.html</original_link>
	<source>SINA</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>SINA Corporation</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://english.sina.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3859709785</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>8</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>CHINA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Sports'>
	    <category>Sports: latest</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
	  <keyword>Sports</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.797908008098602">
	    <location_name>RIO DE JANEIRO</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="BR21" confidence="0.783647000789642">Rio de Janeiro</province>
	    <country fips_code="BR" iso_code="BR" confidence="0.783647000789642">Brazil</country>
	    <subregion>South America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>-22.8999996185303</latitude>
	    <longitude>-43.2332992553711</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.637498021125793">
	    <location_name>Roth</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="GM02" confidence="0.321139991283417">Lower River</province>
	    <country fips_code="GM" iso_code="DE" confidence="0.321139991283417">Germany</country>
	    <subregion>Western Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>50.2167015075684</latitude>
	    <longitude>11.0166997909546</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">he believes the coach will give continuity to the hard work developed and produced in 2010.</property>
                <property name="person">Celso Roth</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">coach</property>
                <property name="person">Celso Roth</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">the coach is a great leader and extremely knowledgeable and a friend to all.</property>
                <property name="person">Celso Roth</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">coach</property>
                <property name="person">Jorge Fossati</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">head coach</property>
                <property name="person">Celso Roth</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">vice president</property>
                <property name="person">Fernando Carvalho</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Fernando Carvalho</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.137</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">coach</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.763</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">vice president</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.137</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">RIO</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.340</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">head coach</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.340</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Jorge Fossati</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.319</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Celso Roth</property>
                <property name="instances">9</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.826</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">Club World Cup</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.521</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsEvent</property>
                <property name="value">World Cup</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.521</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">RIO DE JANEIRO</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.340</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761878">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Turkish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[10:25 Fitch'den Yunanistan’a kredi notu indirme uyarısı]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Fitchâ€™den yapÄ±lan aÃ§Ä±klamada, Yunanistan ile ilgili gÃ¶zden geÃ§irmenin gelecek yÄ±l ocak ayÄ±nda tamamlanacaÄŸÄ±, Yunanistanâ€™Ä±n "BBB-" olan kredi notunu "junk" (Ã§Ã¶p) seviyesine indirilmesi olasÄ±lÄ±ÄŸÄ±nÄ±n arttÄ±ÄŸÄ± belirtildi.Yunanistanâ€™Ä±n "BBB-" olan kredi notunun "junk"seviyesine indirilmesi, kredi notunun yatÄ±rÄ±m yapÄ±labilir seviyenin altÄ±na indiÄŸi anlamÄ±na geliyor.Derecelendirme kuruluÅŸu Fitchâ€™in Yunanistan iÃ§in kredi notu yatÄ±rÄ±m yapÄ±labilir seviyesini en dÃ¼ÅŸÃ¼ÄŸÃ¼ olan "BBB-" dÃ¼zeyinde bulunuyor.UluslararasÄ± derecelendirme kuruluÅŸlarÄ± Moodyâ€™s ve Standard &amp; Poorâ€™s, daha Ã¶nce Yunanistanâ€™Ä±n kredi notunu yatÄ±rÄ±m yapÄ±labilir seviyenin altÄ±na indirilmiÅŸti.Yunanistanâ€™da bugÃ¼n parlamentoda 2011 yÄ±lÄ± bÃ¼tÃ§esi oylanacak.MayÄ±s ayÄ±nda iflasÄ±n eÅŸiÄŸine gelen Yunanistan, AB ve UluslararasÄ± Para Fonunun (IMF) Ã¼Ã§ yÄ±l sÃ¼reli 110 milyar avroluk kurtarma paketini kabul etmiÅŸti.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761878&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.feedsportal.com/c/32727/f/510259/s/10d6211f/l/0L0Smilliyet0N0Btr0Cfitch0Eden0Eyunanistan0Ea0Ekredi0Enotu0Eindirme0Euyarisi0Cekonomi0Csondakika0C220B120B20A10A0C13294840Cdefault0Bhtm/story01.htm</original_link>
	<source>Milliyet</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.feedsportal.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>6</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>TURKEY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761889">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Russian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Российский дипломат выслан из Великобритании за предполагаемый шпионаж]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Сложные отношения Великобритании с Москвой претерпели еще один удар, когда Уильям Хейг объявил о высылке российского дипломата из Лондона в связи с "явными свидетельствами" его шпионской деятельности, пишет The Guardian. 

В коротком заявлении во вторник министр иностранных дел сообщил, что он попросил российское посольство в Лондоне "отозвать из Великобритании члена своего персонала". Ультиматум, выдвинутый 10 декабря, "был ответом на явные свидетельства деятельности российских разведслужб против британских интересов". 

Россия ответила 16 декабря высылкой дипломата из британского посольства в Москве, сообщил Хейг. "Мы не видим никаких оснований для этого поступка", - добавил он. 

"Взаимная высылка дипломатов создала крайне неловкую ситуацию для Хейга, призывавшего к улучшению отношений с Кремлем, которые он при предыдущем лейбористском правительстве были, по его словам, "очень плохими", пишут авторы статьи Люк Гардинг, Ричард Нортон-Тейлор и Том Парфитт.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761889&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.inopressa.ru/article/22Dec2010/guardian/spy1.html</original_link>
	<source>InoPressa</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.inopressa.ru</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>RUSSIA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761896">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Szabályozási kérdések rendezését javasolja az ÁSZ a színházak állami támogatása kapcsán]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Független Hírügynökség]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[A nemzeti kulturális intézmények köréről, feladatairól és támogatási elveiről szóló jogi szabályozás kidolgozását javasolja az Állami Számvevőszék (ÁSZ). 

A nemzeti kulturális intézmények köréről, feladatairól és támogatási elveiről szóló jogi szabályozás kidolgozását javasolja az Állami Számvevőszék (ÁSZ). A színházak 2006 és 2009 közötti állami támogatásának és gazdálkodásának ellenőrzéséről szóló jelentés megállapítja, hogy az előadó-művészeti törvény hatályba lépését követően a támogatási rendszer a korábbinál átláthatóbbá vált, a központi színház-támogatás jelenlegi rendszere ugyanakkor nem veszi figyelembe az ingatlanfenntartás és a fejlesztések pénzügyi igényeit. Az ellenőrzött időszakban egyébként a nézőszám nem változott, az előadások száma pedig növekedett. 

A jelentés megállapítja, hogy a színházak gazdálkodásában az állami támogatás fenntartótól függetlenül a bevételek csaknem kétharmadát tette ki. Ehhez ugyanakkor nem kapcsolódtak elérni kívánt kulturális, társadalmi, gazdasági célok, nem készült az ágazatra vonatkozóan elfogadott stratégia. A vizsgálati anyag arról is beszámol: nem csökkent a regionális színházak közötti különbség. A 100 lakosra jutó színházlátogatások száma a Közép-magyarországi régióban kétszer akkora, mint a Nyugat-dunántúli, és több mint négyszer akkora, mint az Észak-alföldi és Közép-dunántúli régióban. Mindemellett a hazai társulatok nemzetközi jelenléte sem erősödött. 

Az ÁSZ szerint nem szabályozott a kiemelt finanszírozású nemzeti színházi köre, feladatai, támogatási elvei. Jelentős különbségek vannak például az azonos befogadó-képességű, szakmai teljesítményű színházak támogatásában. A dokumentum szerint az előadó-művészeti törvény hatályba lépése után a korábbinál átláthatóbb lett a támogatási rendszer, ugyanakkor nem veszik figyelembe az ingatlanfenntartás és a fejlesztések pénzügyi igényeit. Hátrányos helyzetbe kerülnek például az elavult infrastruktúrával, forráshiányos fenntartóval rendelkező színházak, mivel alacsonyabb összegű fenntartói hozzájárulás esetén a központi forrásból is kevesebbet kapnak. 

A jelentés arra is kitér: a független szervezetek pályázati úton többnyire működésre kaptak támogatást és nem produkciókra. A kiírásokban ugyanakkor gyakran hiányzott a célok és feltételek pontos meghatározása, a számonkérés pedig nem volt teljes körű. 

Az ÁSZ azt javasolja, hogy készüljön el az ágazat céljait is magában foglaló kulturális stratégia és az arra épülő cselekvési terv. Emellett a nemzeti kulturális intézmények köréről, feladatairól és támogatási elvéről szóló jogi szabályozást sürgetnek. A vizsgálati anyag szerint pontosítani kell a pályázati támogatások felhasználhatóságát, a cél szerinti ütemezést és ellenőrizni kell a szabályszerű felhasználást.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761896&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221953</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>5</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XHKG">
	    <name>G.A. Holdings Ltd.</name>
	    <symbol>08126</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761897">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Spanish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA['El Galán Fantasma',  en los Teatros del Canal]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[MADRID, 22 Dic. (EUROPA PRESS) - 

La Comunidad de Madrid presenta 'El Galán Fantasma', de Calderón de la Barca, un referente de humor en los clásicos que forma parte de la programación familiar del Gobierno regional en estas fiestas navideñas, ha informado la Comunidad de Madrid. 

Dirigida por Mariano de Paco, experto en teatro clásico, estará en la Sala Verde de los Teatros del Canal desde hoy hasta el domingo 9 de enero. 

La representación ofrece un reparto de lujo, que cuenta con la colaboración especial del gran actor Manuel Gallardo (en el papel de Enrique, padre de Astolfo, uno de los protagonistas de esta comedia de enredo), y los actores Patxi Freytez, Carmen Morales (hija de la recordada cantante Rocío Dúrcal), Guillermo Montesinos, Alejandro Arestegui, Ana Ruiz y Juan Calot.

En la presentación de este montaje, que ha tenido lugar hoy en los Teatros del Canal, han participado el director general de Promoción Cultural de la Comunidad de Madrid, Amado Giménez; el director artístico de los Teatros del Canal, Albert Boadella; el director de esta representación, Mariano de Paco, y todo el elenco de la obra.

La adaptación teatral del clásico de Calderón de la Barca es obra de Eduardo Galán y Daniel Pérez, cuyo trabajo se ha centrado en mostrar sobre el escenario la tan calderoniana apariencia engañosa del mundo.

Sobre esta idea, el director, Mariano de Paco, influido de alguna forma por la vertiente del cómic, ha conseguido plasmar persecuciones, misterio, humor, duelos, amoríos imposibles y confusión en un escenario, todo ello bañado con tintes de humor. 

La obra se rodea también de un gran equipo artístico, con un iluminador como Nicolás Fitchtel, el escenógrafo David de Loaysa y un diseño de vestuario que corre a cargo de Mayka Chamorro, realizado por Cornejo.

HISTORIA DE ENREDOS CON FINAL FELIZ

El 'galán fantasma' es una comedia de enredo y misterio que narra con humor una historia de capa y espada llena de persecuciones y amores. El Duque de Sajonia, el poderoso cruel, cree dar muerte al protagonista, Astolfo, el caballero enamorado de la dama (Julia) ante los ojos de todos.

Cuando Enrique, padre de Astolfo, descubre que su hijo no está muerto, lo esconde fuera de la ciudad. Recuperado de sus heridas, Astolfo se aparece, como si fuera un fantasma, en el jardín de la casa de Julia por un pasadizo secreto, creando la confusión en todos los personajes, menos en su dama, conocedora del secreto. 

Como en todas las comedias de la época, El galán fantasma termina con el final feliz del casamiento del galán y la dama. Calderón de la Barca recoge en esta comedia una de las constantes del teatro barroco: la apariencia engañosa del mundo. 

A través del enredo característico en el que se ven sumidos los personajes se explica de manera cómica la complicación del conocimiento. El galán fantasma es una comedia cuyos protagonistas se ven implicados en la convención social del sometimiento a la autoridad, representada por El Duque, que se interpone en su relación sentimental, ya que él mismo está enamorado de la dama, Julia.

Esto llevará a un enfrentamiento entre el primer galán, Astolfo, y El Duque, que deparará un juego de equívocos, de fingimientos, apariciones y urgencias para desembocar en el final feliz que desde el comienzo de la obra se espera. 

Aunque, a veces, el drama parezca cernirse sobre las cabezas de estos personajes, un nuevo giro a la confusión disuelve la angustia y precipita el deseado encuentro feliz en los versos finales.

Mariano de Paco, un experto en el mundo clásico Mariano de Paco, director de este montaje, abandonó su faceta de actor (que empezó a cultivar a las órdenes de César Oliva en el Aula de Teatro de la Universidad de Murcia) para dedicarse a la dirección teatral. 

Como gestor, ha ocupado la gerencia del Festival Internacional de Teatro Clásico de Almagro, de 2003 a 2007. Posteriormente, ha sido nombrado director de la Feria de Artes Escénicas de Madrid (ARTEMADferia), constituida por empresas productoras de artes escénicas de la Comunidad de Madrid, que cuenta actualmente con unas 30 compañías asociadas.

Entre los reconocimientos que ha recibido en su fructífera carrera se encuentra el notorio Premio José Luis Alonso para Jóvenes Directores de Escena, otorgado en 2005 por la Asociación de Directores de Escena (ADE) por la obra Danny y Roberta, de John Patrick Shanley. 

Una representación que además consiguió el premio a la Mejor Actriz (Maite Jiménez) y el Premio Ibercaja al mejor espectáculo en el certamen Arcipreste de Hita de Guadalajara en 2006 y el premio al Mejor Actor (Francesc Galcerán) en la 12ª muestra de Teatre de Barcelona de 2007, en la que también fue finalista al de Mejor Espectáculo.

Entre sus últimas direcciones, se encuentran 'Felices 30' (2009), 'Obsession Street' (2009), 'La fierecilla domada' (2008), de William Shakespeare, o 'La señorita' de Trévelez (2007), de Carlos Arniches, con la que realizó una larga y exitosa gira.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761897&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.europapress.es/madrid/noticia-teatros-canal-acogen-hoy-galan-fantasma-clasico-mas-gamberro-calderon-20101222061223.html</original_link>
	<source>Europa Press</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.europapress.es</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>6</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>SPAIN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XPAR">
	    <name>Canal+</name>
	    <symbol>AN</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="point" class="Hypsographic" mentions="1" confidence="0.985705971717834">
	    <location_name>El Galn</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP31" confidence="0.317288994789124">Murcia Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.317288994789124">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>37.6833000183105</latitude>
	    <longitude>-0.733332991600037</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="unknown" class="Locality or Area" mentions="2" confidence="0.852707982063293">
	    <location_name>Comunidad de Madrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.750532984733582">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.750532984733582">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4178009033203</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.7022500038147</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="province" class="Administrative region" mentions="2" confidence="0.893308997154236">
	    <location_name>Comunidad de Madrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.892888009548187">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.892888009548187">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.5</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.66667008399963</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="populated locality" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.81183797121048">
	    <location_name>Sajonia</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="CO12" confidence="0.516771972179413">Cordoba</province>
	    <country fips_code="CO" iso_code="CO" confidence="0.516771972179413">Colombia</country>
	    <subregion>South America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>8.50333023071289</latitude>
	    <longitude>-75.5911026000977</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.996868014335632">
	    <location_name>Madrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.951202988624573">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.951202988624573">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4000015258789</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.68333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.735338985919952">
	    <location_name>Guadalajara</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP54" confidence="0.732205986976624">Castilla-La Mancha Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.732205986976624">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.63330078125</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.16667008399963</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.985993981361389">
	    <location_name>Barcelona</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP56" confidence="0.484863013029099">Catalua Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.484863013029099">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>41.38330078125</latitude>
	    <longitude>2.18333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761899">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Hyperbaric oxygen ameliorates worsening signs and symptoms of post-traumatic stress disorder]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Eovaldi B et al. – The authors propose that hyperbaric oxygen was effective in improving the patient's neuropsychiatric symptoms by reducing cerebral oxidative stress, inflammation, vasogenic edema, and hippocampal neuronal apoptosis. Further investigation into the use of hyperbaric oxygen as a novel therapy for the secondary prevention of post–traumatic stress disorder that often accompanies postconcussive syndrome may be warranted. They acknowledge that hyperbaric oxygen therapy has been shown to have a strong placebo effect on neurologic and psychiatric diseases.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761899&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.mdlinx.com/PsychLinx/xml-article.cfm/3405392</original_link>
	<source>MDLinx</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.mdlinx.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:02AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>15</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>HealthCare</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Medical</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP35</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS62</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">post-traumatic stress</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.405</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Technology</property>
                <property name="value">apoptosis</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.405</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">postconcussive syndrome</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.329</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">IndustryTerm</property>
                <property name="value">prevention of post?traumatic stress disorder</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.329</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalTreatment</property>
                <property name="value">hyperbaric oxygen therapy</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.202</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">inflammation</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.405</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">neurologic and psychiatric diseases</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.202</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">MedicalCondition</property>
                <property name="value">traumatic stress disorder</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.329</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761914">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="German">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[French Nails]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[[Artikel] [Geschlechterrollen] [Sex] [Mode] Frau ist zum ultimativ "Schönsten Geschlecht" mutiert, hat aber ihre Gebärfähigkeit verloren. Unter French Nails riecht es nicht selten etwas faulig 

Femizid ist wieder so ein Wort, das man erfinden müsste, wenn’s das nicht schon längst gäbe. 

Prinzipiell geht’s mir bei diesem gesellschaftlichen Phänomen um die Auslöschung der Weiblichkeit, nicht der Frauen. 

Intuitiv denkt man, dass die ach so holde Weiblichkeit heute lebendiger denn je ist. Nackte Tatsachen springen einem ja bereits von den unzähligen Mode- und Klatschmagazinen am Kiosk in Gesicht. 

Porno ist im Internet nicht mal einen Klick weit entfernt. Und auch in der Fußgängerzone wird nicht mit Reizen gegeizt, vor allem wenn wieder junge Russinnen als Austauschstudentinnen in der Stadt sind. Darf man mal anfassen? 

Warum über Femizid? 

Nun, wenn man es aus der Mikroperspektive betrachtet, ist es einleuchtend, dass es um individuelle Blockaden, Enttäuschungen, Selbsthass oder generell aus psychiatrischer Sicht bedenkliche Dispositionen geht. Manche sagen auch einfach kaputt dazu, und je länger ich darüber nachdenke, desto besser trifft es den Kern. Insgesamt liegt doch einiges im Argen, was frau besser nicht ihren Mitmenschen zumuten sollte. Frauen sind in dieser Hinsicht ohnehin doppelt benachteiligt. Einmal müssen sie sich ständig wehren gegen den Missbrauch ihres Körpers, und dann auch noch gegen den Missbrauch ihrer Seele (was in der Tat oft identisch ist). Daher wird der Weiblichkeit dann, sofern sie nicht schon während der Kindheit vom lieben Daddy heraus gevögelt oder wahlweise heraus geprügelt oder – was wohl der Normalfall ist – einfach nur ignoriert wurde, in einer epischen Materialschlacht der Garaus gemacht. Was wird da nicht alles aufgefahren, von den Jimmy-Choo-High-Heels über das Make-up-Notfallkit von Chanel, bestehend aus Wimperntusche, Concealer und Lipgloss, hin zu einem dekorativen Tattoo auf der Schulter. Frau ist dann final zum ultimativ Schönsten Geschlecht mutiert, hat aber dafür ihre Gebärfähigkeit verloren. Und unter angeschweißten French Nails riecht es mittlerweile nicht selten etwas faulig. 

Kontrollverlust ist eine zweischneidige Sache. Du strebst das gelegentlich an, in dem eigenen Unbehagen darüber, dass die glamouröse Hülle zwar die vollkommenste Inkarnation der Interpretation der eigenen Persönlichkeit ist, aber es irgendwie auch keiner zu würdigen weiß, diese ganze Mühe, die es dich jeden Tag kostet, ein Image in ein Leben zu verwandeln. Jedenfalls bist du also doch mal schwach geworden, und hast dich für ein paar Stunden deiner Weiblichkeit hingegeben, die zwar ein bisschen verkümmert war, aber durchaus noch vorhanden. 

Am nächsten Morgen habe ich dich gefragt, ob du beautytechnisch für den Rest deines Lebens gewappnet bist. Du hast das direkt als Angriff gewertet. Dabei sahst du echt klasse aus, so ganz ohne Make-up und Klamotten. Schade. Hast dich aufgebretzelt und bist gegangen. Tschüssi. 

Aber ehrlich: Wenn man sich schon mit dem Nickname Versaut_18 in einem Chatraum für Fußballfans angemeldet hat, dann sind die Erwartungen halt dementsprechend niedrig. Musst du auch verstehn. 

Heidegger würde einwerfen: „Der Mensch ist der Platzhalter des Nichts.“ 

Meiner Meinung nach ist das aber noch zu milde gesprochen. 

„Diese Frau ist das Nichts“, macht mehr Sinn. Von meiner Seite her gesehen. Weil ich die andere nicht kenne.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761914&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.neon.de/kat/sehen/gesellschaft/geschlechterrollen/327326.html</original_link>
	<source>NEON.de</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.neon.de</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>GERMANY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Lifestyle</keyword>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
	  <keyword>Health</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XBOM">
	    <name>PVP Ventures Ltd</name>
	    <symbol>517556</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XNSE">
	    <name>PVP Ventures Ltd</name>
	    <symbol>PVP</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761918">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Italian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Mariano: pochi acquistipesano crisi e viabilità]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[pesano crisi e viabilità 

MARIANO COMENSE - Addobbi e luminarie in centro, ma sin qui pochi gli acquisti (Foto by BARTESAGHI) 

MARIANO Freddo polare in città, non tanto per le temperature artiche che hanno investito Mariano in queste ore, ma piuttosto per l'andamento delle vendite natalizie. Nei negozi, infatti, il clima è tutt'altro che caldo: dal ristagno degli acquisti si salvano solo i telefonini e i gioielli, mentre l'abbigliamento, le calzature, la pelletteria e i computer oscillano tra giornate sì e altre drammaticamente negative. Colpa della crisi? Delle tredicesime in ritardo o meno ricche degli anni passati? Di una viabilità che non facilità - secondo alcuni -  il raggiungimento dei negozi del centro? Tutte ipotesi, ma nessuna risposta certa, tranne una costatazione che mette d'accordo tutti: «Questo Natale non è lontanamente paragonabile a quelli passati». 

Ne è convinta Loredana Grassi della pelletteria “Ellegi” di piazza Roma: «E' davvero un Natale molto freddo sotto tutti i punti di vista - spiega -: le vendite si muovono poco e quanto siano in meno rispetto l'anno scorso lo vedremo solo alla fine, ma la sensazione è che lo stacco sia netto. Non vediamo interesse all'acquisto, mentre l'anno scorso già all'inizio di dicembre si capiva che c'era il desiderio di comprare: adesso la gente guarda le vetrine e basta. Sicuramente la crisi ha il suo peso in questo perché le famiglie hanno meno soldi da spendere, ma personalmente rimango convinta che il problema maggiore sia stato consentire che i saldi partano il 6 gennaio. Gli sconti così anticipati compromettono non solo il Natale, ma l'intera stagione». Di umore diverso, invece, Giampiero Bizzozzero, titolare del negozio di calzature e pelletteria Du Pass di viale Lombardia: «Le vendite hanno iniziato a riprendersi dalla scorsa primavera e da allora il trend è stato costante - dichiara -: certo, non si può paragonare la stagione attuale a quelle passate quando a una scarpa di un certo valore quasi sempre si abbinava una borsa della stessa importanza. Adesso si compra o l'uno o l'altra e inoltre ho notato che la classe media ha fatto un passo indietro rispetto a certi marchi: mentre prima voleva solo scarpe firmate, adesso capisce che forse è meglio guardare alla qualità di una calzatura e quindi i nostri produttori italiani hanno saputo dare la risposta giusta. Inoltre la clientela ha capito che a volte spendere troppo poco non significa risparmiare, ma comprare un prodotto di scarsa qualità e infine noto maggiore consapevolezza anche verso i saldi. La gente preferisce comprare per tempo, quando sa che può trovare proprio quello che cerca, piuttosto che aspettare le vendite e doversi accontentare di qualcosa di completamente diverso e a volte pure sbagliato». Perplessi, invece, sono i gestori della Cartolibreria Anna di via Risorgimento dove è possibile comprare libri e dell'oggettistica per dei regali natalizi: «Rispetto all'anno scorso le vendite sono sicuramente calate, ma sinceramente non riusciamo a darci una spiegazione del perché. Forse la risposta sta in una serie di elementi che vanno dalla viabilità stravolta in piazza Roma con il senso unico a scendere, che indubbiamente ha eliminato i potenziali clienti di passaggio di prima, la carenza di parcheggi, i problemi dei tanti lavoratori finiti in cassa integrazione, le scadenze da pagare in dicembre tra tasse e mutui e forse le tredicesime date in ritardo rispetto agli altri anni. Notiamo che molte persone ci chiedono di mettere da parte degli articoli perché al momento non hanno la possibilità di acquistare e comunque prima di spendere ci pensano sopra diverse volte. I motivi possono essere tanti e tutti validi, ma di sicuro un Natale così freddo nelle vendite non si vedeva da tempo».]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761918&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it/stories/Cronaca/175497_mariano_pochi_acquisti_pesano_crisi_e_viabilit/</original_link>
	<source>La Provincia di Como</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>9</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>ITALY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761923">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="French">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Laurent Gbagbo, sourd aux appels, réaffirme être le président]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Publié le mercredi 22 décembre 2010 � 07H25 par Tim Cocks

ABIDJAN (Reuters) - Laurent Gbagbo a réaffirmé mardi soir lors d'une intervention � la télévision d'Etat ivoirienne (RTI) qu'il avait remporté l'élection présidentielle et a invité un "comité d'évaluation" international � venir vérifier la validité des résultats du scrutin du 28 novembre.

Ce comité dirigé par un représentant de l'Union africaine comprendrait des représentants de la Cedeao, de l'UA, de la Ligue arabe, des Nations unies, des Etats-Unis, de l'Union européenne, de la Russie et de la Chine, a-t-il précisé.

"Je ne veux plus que le sang soit versé, je ne veux plus de guerre", a expliqué Laurent Gbagbo dans son discours, retransmis � Paris par la chaîne iTélé. "Je suis donc prêt dans le respect de la Constitution (...) � accueillir un comité d'évaluation post-électoral", a ajouté le président sortant.

Ce comité aurait pour mission "d'analyser objectivement" le processus électoral "pour un règlement pacifique de la crise", a-t-il expliqué.

Laurent Gbagbo, qui refuse de quitter le pouvoir après le second tour remporté, selon la communauté internationale, par son rival Alassane Ouattara, subit des pressions de plus en plus fortes.

"J'ai remporté le scrutin, je suis le président de la République de Côte d'Ivoire", a-t-il cependant réaffirmé mardi soir, soulignant que "l'Etat fonctionne".

Selon lui, "la communauté internationale déclare la guerre � la Côte d'Ivoire". "Cela n'est pas acceptable et cela ne sera pas accepté", a-t-il mis en garde.

Il a estimé que tôt ou tard, la force de l'Onu et le dispositif français Licorne "partiront" et a appelé le camp de son rival Alassane Ouattara � quitter l'hôtel d'Abidjan où il est actuellement retranché.

SITUATION DANGEREUSE POUR L'ONUCI

Des diplomates ont expliqué ne pas prendre au sérieux la déclaration du président sortant et ont précisé que ni les Etats-Unis, ni la France ou d'autres Etats n'ont été consultés.

"Au fond, il ne s'agit que d'une stratégie pour gagner du temps. Gbagbo doit se soumettre � la décision des électeurs telle qu'elle a été certifiée", a dit un diplomate.

Les chefs d'Etat de la Cedeao doivent se retrouver pour un sommet vendredi dans la capitale nigériane, Abuja, pour discuter des derniers développements en Côte d'Ivoire.

Malgré les restrictions imposées par les Etats-Unis aux déplacements de plusieurs dirigeants ivoiriens et malgré un nouvel appel de la France pour exiger le départ de Gbagbo, ses partisans ne semblent rien vouloir lâcher sur le terrain.

La mission de l'Onuci apparaît de plus en plus délicate et dangereuse mais celle-ci va se poursuivre, a annoncé Alain Leroy, secrétaire général adjoint de l'Onu.

Dans un entretien diffusé mardi par Lefigaro.fr, Alain Leroy explique que le camp Gbagbo fait tout pour couper l'approvisionnement des casques bleus en fioul et en nourriture.

"Nous avons encore des réserves, mais la situation devient de plus en plus délicate et dangereuse" pour la force de l'Onu, affirme-t-il.

Pour le secrétaire général des Nations unies, Ban Ki-moon, les forces loyales � Laurent Gbagbo tentent d'imposer un blocus aux soldats de l'Onuci.

Rendant compte devant l'Assemblée générale de l'Onu, Ban a demandé aux Etats membres des Nations unies de se préparer � contribuer � ce que les fournitures parviennent � l'Onuci, dont les hommes protègent notamment l'hôtel du Golf où est retranché Alassane Ouattara.

"L'intention de M. Gbagbo et des forces de sécurité qui lui sont loyales est manifestement d'imposer un blocus � la mission des casques bleus des Nations unies et d'étrangler le gouvernement du président élu Ouattara", a dit Ban.

Lundi le Conseil de sécurité avait décidé de prolonger la mission des 10.000 casques bleus présents dans le pays.

Le Nigeria a procédé � l'évacuation de l'ensemble de ses diplomates en poste en Côte d'Ivoire et va rapatrier ses ressortissants � la suite d'une attaque contre son ambassade.

En dépit des tensions, un porte-parole de l'armée ivoirienne a annoncé � la télévision que le couvre-feu instauré juste après le second tour de la présidentielle sera levé mercredi. Selon l'Onu, au moins 50 personnes ont été tuées dans des violences et des centaines ont été blessées ou enlevées.

Gérard Bon et Pierre Sérisier pour le service français

Avertissement Nous vous rappelons que vous avez, lors de la création de votre compte, accepté les conditions d’utilisation du site. Celles-ci proscrivent notamment la diffamation, l’incitation � la haine raciale, l’atteinte aux bonnes mœurs. Nous vous prions donc de respecter strictement . A défaut, votre compte sera banni du site. Voir aussi : Droits de reproduction et de diffusion rservs � www.paris-normandie.fr]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761923&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.paris-normandie.fr/article/france-monde/laurent-gbagbo-sourd-aux-appels-reaffirme-etre-le-president</original_link>
	<source>Paris-Normandie</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.paris-normandie.fr</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860374639</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>3</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>FRANCE</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="MTAA">
	    <name>Cembre</name>
	    <symbol>CMB</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XPAR">
	    <name>SES S.A.</name>
	    <symbol>SESG</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XLUX">
	    <name>SES S.A.</name>
	    <symbol>28734</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761924">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Turkish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[10:25 Ersan double double yaptı]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Maverics’te Caron Butler 20, Dirk Nowitzki 17 sayıyla oynarken, Jason Kidd, maçı 13 sayı 12 asistle tamamladı. 

Önceki gece Miami Heat’in 12 maçlık galibiyet serisine son veren Maverics, aynı başarılı performansı dün akşam da sürdürdü ve 2 sayılık atışlarda yüzde 50, 3 sayılık atışlarda ise yüzde 46’lık başarı oranı yakaladı. 

Kadrosuna kattığı yeni isimlerle tekrar yapılanma sürecine giren evsahibi ekipte ise Dwight Howard, attığı attığı 26 sayıyla hem takımının hem de sahanın en skorer ismi oldu. Howard, 23 de ribaund alarak "double double" yaptı. JJ Reddick 21 sayıyla oynarken, Hidayet Türkoğlu maçı 9 sayı 8 asist 1 ribaunt ile tamamladı. 

Bir diğer maçta Chicago Bulls ile Philadelphia 76ers karşı karşıya geldi. 

Maça Joakim Noah ve Taj Gibson’dan yoksun çıkan Bulls, evinde oynadığı maçı 45 sayı farkla, 121-76 kazanmayı başardı. Bulls’da Carlos Boozer 16 sayı 11 ribaund, Derrick Rose ise 22 sayı 12 asist ile galibiyette büyük rol oynadı. Takımın bir diğer skorer ismi, rakip potaya 22 sayı bırakan Luol Deng oldu. Bulls’un Türk basketbolcusu Ömer Aşık ise maçı 8 sayı 6 ribaund ile tamamladı. 

76ers’da Andre Iguodala 17 sayıyla oynadı. Chicago Bulls, bu sonuçla son 9 maçta 8. galibiyetini almış oldu. 

Bir diğer Türk basketbolcu Ersan İlyasova’nın formasını giydiği Milwakuee Bucks ise dün gece Staples Center’da Los Angeles Lakers’a konuk oldu. 

İlyasova’nın oldukça iyi bir performans sergilediği maçta Bucks, rakibine 98-79 ile üstünlük sağladı. 

Sahanın en skorer ismi, 22 sayıyla oynayan Bucks oyuncusu Earl Boykins oldu. Takım arkadaşı John Salmons, geceyi 20 sayıyla tamamlarken, Ersan İlyasova, 17 sayı 11 ribaund ile "double double" yaparak galibiyete büyük bir katkı sağladı. 

         Los Angeles Lakers’da ise Kobe Bryant geceyi 21 sayıyla tamamladı. 

         Gecenin diğer maçlarında şu sonuçlar alındı: 

         Charlotte Bobcats: 81 - Oklahoma City Thunder: 99 

         Memphis Grizzlies: 94 - New Jersey Nets: 101 

         Sacramento Kings: 109 - Golden State Warriors: 117]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761924&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.feedsportal.com/c/32727/f/510259/s/10d6211e/l/0Lspor0Bmilliyet0N0Btr0Cersan0Edouble0Edouble0Eyapti0Cspor0Cspordetay0C220B120B20A10A0C13294830Cdefault0Bhtm/story01.htm</original_link>
	<source>Milliyet</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.feedsportal.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>7</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>TURKEY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XNAS">
	    <name>Comcast Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>CMCSK</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XNAS">
	    <name>Comcast Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>CMCSA</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="MTAA">
	    <name>Industria Macchine Automatiche SPA</name>
	    <symbol>IMA</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761936">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Leragasztotta egyik szemhéját Gábor Zsazsa férje]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Független Hírügynökség]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Kórházba kellett vinni kedden a súlyosan beteg Gábor Zsazsa férjét, miután leragasztotta egyik szemhéját - közölte a celebportál, a TMZ.com. 

Kórházba kellett vinni kedden a súlyosan beteg Gábor Zsazsa férjét, miután leragasztotta egyik szemhéját - közölte a celebportál, a TMZ.com. A 93 éves, magyar származású egykori színésznőt az utóbbi hónapokban többször vitték kórházba, miközben elterjedt a hír, hogy haldoklik, ezúttal azonban a hercegi címmel büszkélkedő, von Anhalt került bajba, miután egy műköröm-ragasztó véletlenül rákerült a szemhéjára, és megkötött. 

A 66 éves, német származású Frederic von Anhalt szemét az egyik Beverly Hills klinikán nyitották fel. A férfi egyik munkatársa azt mondta a celebportálnak, hogy von Anhalt végig jókedvű volt a kezelés idején. 

Alig két hónappal ezelőtt volt egy másik bizarr balesete is a férfinak. Akkor azért került kórházba, mert állítólag lenyelt egy méhecskét, amikor napozás közben palacsintát falatozott házuk hátsó kertjében. 

Gábor Zsazsa kilencszer kötött házasságot és hétszer vált el. Jelenlegi férjével, Friedrich (Frederic) von Anhalttal, 1986. augusztus 14-én volt az esküvő. Von Anhalt Mária Auguszta anhalti hercegnőnek, II. Vilmos császár menyének 1980-ban adoptált fia, és így lett belőle herceg. Gábor Zsazsának ez az eddigi leghosszabb házassága. 

Von Anhalt 2007. február 9-én bejelentette, hogy évtizeden át tartó viszonya volt az egy nappal korábban elhunyt Anna Nicole Smith-szel, a Playboy egykori modell-színésznőjével, és lehet, hogy ő Smith lányának apja. Végül kiderült, hogy Smith öthónapos lányának nem Anhalt az édesapja. A 66 éves férfi 2010. január 21-én azzal állt elő, hogy indulni kíván a kaliforniai kormányzóválasztásokon.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761936&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221951</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>6</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XHKG">
	    <name>G.A. Holdings Ltd.</name>
	    <symbol>08126</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761937">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Novák: kormányfőt is váltottunk már évad közben]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[hvg@hvg.hu]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[A Jobbik alelnöke szerint Alföldi Róbertet, a Nemzeti Színház vezetőjét azért nem merik meneszteni, mert félnek az antiszemitizmus és a homofóbia vádjától.  /* hvg.hu - 200x200 A */    A Jobbik alelnöke a Magyar Televízió Ma reggel című műsorában arra a felvetésre, hogy Alföldi Róbertet, a Nemzeti Színház vezetőjét miért személyében támadják, ahelyett, hogy szakmailag kritizálnák, Novák Előd elmondta: nemrég meg akarta nézni Závada Pál darabját, de visszamondta a jegyrendelést, mert egy kritikában azt olvasta, hogy a színpadon az Erdélybe bevonuló bakák maszturbálnak a Nagy-Magyarország képre. Hangsúlyozta: azt tapasztalják, hogy Alföldit azért nem merik leváltani, mert félnek attól, hogy akkor antiszemitizmus, homofóbia vádjával illetnék őket. Pedig – tette hozzá – miniszterelnököt is váltottunk már évad közben. Örömmel vették – mondta Novák előd. (A Kossuth rádió 180 perc című műsorának vezetője egy percre elhallgatott, miután a parlament elfogadta a médiatörvényt.) Novák úgy véli: a médiafelügyeletben ott kell lennie minden párt képviselőjének. Szerinte a Fidesz kaotikus viszonyok között rendezte a médiatörvényt. Az utolsó pillanatban, amikor csak koherenciazavarra hivatkozva lehetett benyújtani módosító indítványt, összesen 106 érkezett az asztalukra, ezt elolvasni is lehetetlen egy óra alatt – szögezte le.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761937&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://hvg.hu/itthon/20101222_alfoldi_homofob_vadak#rss</original_link>
	<source>Hvg.hu</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://hvg.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761943">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Exploring the role of personality in the relationship between maximization and well-being]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[My Library Conferences Resources Jobs MDLinx Blog CME Articles Full Text Articles Evidence Based Medicine Articles Clinical Articles]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761943&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.mdlinx.com/PsychLinx/xml-article.cfm/3405807</original_link>
	<source>MDLinx</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.mdlinx.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:02AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>17</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>HealthCare</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Medical</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP35</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS62</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761951">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Italian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Cantù, cambio tra i vigilise ne va il comandante]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[se ne va il comandante 

CANTU' - Lucio Dioguardi lascia il comando della polizia locale di Cantù per andare a Paderno Dugnano (Foto by Carlo Pozzoni) 

CANTU' I vigili rimangono senza comandante, anche se per l'ufficialità manca ancora qualche giorno. Lucio Dioguardi, infatti, sta per lasciare vuota la sua scrivania al comando di via Vittorio Veneto per raggiungere il comune di Paderno Dugnano. 

La notizia, in realtà, arriva proprio dal Comune in provincia di Milano, dove si è concluso il concorso per cercare il nuovo responsabile della polizia locale dopo che il precedente comandante, Giorgio Grandesso, è andato ad occupare un posto in amministrazione provinciale nel settore della Protezione civile. 

Concorso al quale ha partecipato anche Dioguardi. Lunedì, all'albo del comune di Paderno Dugnano, è stato esposto il risultato del concorso, e il comandante canturino è risultato il vincitore, superando gli altri tre candidati. A questo punto, bisogna solo attendere la lettera di nomina da parte dell'amministrazione comunale di Paderno, che dovrebbe essere recapitata a Lucio Dioguardi nei prossimi giorni. 

Il trasferimento del comandante potrebbe arrivare nel giro di pochi giorni, forse entro la fine dell'anno. Per quanto riguarda il comune di Cantù, ci potrebbero essere dei problemi nei primi mesi del 2011. E' infatti possibile che per alcuni mesi - forse addirittura sei - il posto di Dioguardi potrebbe rimanere formalmente vuoto, con soluzioni temporanee interne.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761951&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it/stories/Cronaca/175479_cant_cambio_tra_i_vigili_se_ne_va_il_comandante/</original_link>
	<source>La Provincia di Como</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>8</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>ITALY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XLON">
	    <name>Arriva PLC</name>
	    <symbol>ARI</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761952">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[AAC Secures 40 Acres for New River Gorge Climbersâ Campground]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[AAC Secures 40 Acres for New River Gorge Climbers’ Campground 

12/21/10 – The American Alpine Club (AAC) has purchased 40 acres of land in Fayetteville, West Virginia, within walking distance of rock climbing at the New River Gorge. The AAC’s plan is to build a campground for climbers at this location. 

This purchase was made possible by the generosity of AAC donors along with other financing. Notably, just over one-third of the funding was a loan from the Access Fund Land Conservation Campaign. The property was chosen by local climbers and the New River Alliance of Climbers. 

Providing lodging facilities is central to the AAC’s vision of supporting the climbing way of life by improving benefits for members and other climbers, said AAC Executive Director Phil Powers: “We are building on the tradition that started with the Grand Teton Climbers’ Ranch. Lodging options within walking distance from great climbing supports the climbing lifestyle we all enjoy. We hope to create a facility that meets climbers’ needs and adds opportunities for climbers to gather and share their stories.” 

The campground will be located a short walk from numerous popular cliffs. In addition to the parcel’s central cragging location, limited bouldering exists on-site. Completion of the campground is expected to take at least two years. 

The proposed campground is expected to house 50-60 campsites, bathrooms and showers, a cooking pavilion, library or meeting space, and manager’s quarters. As with other AAC campgrounds, the property will be developed specifically with climbers in mind and will allow for extended stays at inexpensive rates. 

About The American Alpine Club - The American Alpine Club provides knowledge and inspiration, conservation and advocacy, and logistical support for the climbing community. The Club manages a climbers’ campground in Grand Teton National Park, publishes the world’s most sought after annual climbing publication, the American Alpine Journal, cares for the world’s leading mountaineering library and offers annual climbing, conservation, and research grants to budding adventurers. Learn about additional programs and become a member at americanalpineclub.org. Join the AAC’s online community at facebook.com/americanalpineclub. 

About the Access Fund Land Conservation Campaign - The Access Fund Land Conservation Campaign (AFLCC) is the first-ever multimillion-dollar revolving loan program that gives local climbing organizations and other agencies the money and power they need to act swiftly to protect valuable climbing resources. The AFLCC provides short-term loans and transaction expertise to enable rapid protection of at-risk climbing locations through direct acquisitions, leases, easements, and other tactics. By providing this expertise and bridge financing for time-sensitive projects, the AFLCC gives climbing organizations the opportunities to finalize take-out strategies or raise money over a longer period of time. The AFLCC also offers grants for direct conservation efforts, including acquisitions and other projects that protect climbing areas on private land. More at accessfund.org/aflcc.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761952&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.climbing.com/news/press/aac_secures_40_acres_for_new_river_gorge_climbers_campground</original_link>
	<source>Climbing Magazine</source>
	<source_category>Consumer</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.climbing.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860084637</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>2</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Recreation</keyword>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="PINX">
	    <name>Logistical Support, Inc.</name>
	    <symbol>LGSL</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">Providing lodging facilities is central to the AAC?s vision of supporting the climbing way of life by improving benefits for members and other climbers</property>
                <property name="persondescription">Executive Director, American Alpine Club</property>
                <property name="person">Phil Powers</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">Executive Director</property>
                <property name="person">Phil Powers</property>
                <property name="organization">American Alpine Club</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Executive Director</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.228</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">NaturalFeature</property>
                <property name="value">New River Gorge</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.330</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Phil Powers</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.228</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">New River Alliance of Climbers</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.267</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">PublishedMedium</property>
                <property name="value">the American Alpine Journal</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.093</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">manager</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.187</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">Fayetteville</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.330</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">ProvinceOrState</property>
                <property name="value">West Virginia</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.330</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">IndustryTerm</property>
                <property name="value">online community</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.075</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">American Alpine Club</property>
                <property name="instances">11</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.871</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761959">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Mother Of All New Year's Event 2011]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[at The Regency Ballroom,  San Francisco, CA 

Price: $55 - 100 

Age Suitability: 21 and up 

Tags:  music, club, san francisco, dj, entertainment, new years, fun, house, event, djs, nightlife, groups, discounts, cheap, open bar, mash, ups, pary, kelley james, mike posner 

MOANY has been San Francisco's most entertaining New Year's Eve Event. We have been successfuly ranked in the "Nations Top 10 Best NYE Event in the Nation" by AOL 4 years in a row. Last year we were ranked #7 in the Nation. 

Buy tickets directly from me for $55.00 general admission tickets and $100 open bar vip. To find out more info email at djbencabanas@hotmail.com 

Electronic tickets and table service can be purchased here at http://moanynye-bencabanas.eventbrite.com/ 

Event Website 

Categories: Clubs, Hip-Hop 

Creator: djbencabanas 

Creator: djbencabanas 

Performers at this Event 

Mike Posner 

Mike Posner is a pop and hip-hop artist. 

Location &amp; Nearby Info 

1290 Sutter St. 

San Francisco, CA 94109 

(415) 673-5716 

Full map and directions 

Show nearby: 

Reviews &amp; Comments 

USER REVIEWS 

This event currently has no reviews. Be the first to share your thoughts with others! 

Don't Miss This 

Sponsored Listings 

at Imperial Palace 

Fri 12/24 7:00p 

at San Jose Center for the Performing Arts 

Wed 12/22 1:30p 

Hot Tickets  More » 

ON SALE NOW 

Fri 12/24 7:00p 

Wed 12/22 6:00p 

Tue 12/28 8:00p 

Sat 1/15 8:00p 

Fri 12/31 8:00p 

Tue 1/18 7:30p 

ON SALE SOON 

On Sale: Tue 12/28 

Fri 2/4 8:00p 

Other Events 

at The Regency Ballroom 

12/31 

7:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

12/31 

9:00p 

San Francisco Related Topics: 

clubs | hip-hop | new year's eve | civic center san francisco | new year san francisco | new year in san francisco | civic center san francisco events | new year events san francisco | moany discount | live music new years san francisco | electronic music san francisco | ballroom new years san francisco | music new years eve san francisco]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761959&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://events.sfgate.com/san-francisco-ca/events/show/155474545-mother-of-all-new-years-event-2011</original_link>
	<source>San Francisco Chronicle</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>Events</genre>
	<publisher>Hearst Communications</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://events.sfgate.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Feb  2 2011  1:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>71</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'US regional'>
	    <category>San Francisco Bay Area news</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XNYS">
	    <name>Time Warner, Inc.</name>
	    <symbol>TWX</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>San Francisco, CA</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US06" confidence="0.491450995206833">California</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.491450995206833">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>37.7700004577637</latitude>
	    <longitude>-122.449996948242</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.998654007911682">
	    <location_name>san francisco</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US06" confidence="0.261743992567062">California</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.261743992567062">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>37.7700004577637</latitude>
	    <longitude>-122.449996948242</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="0.993129014968872">
	    <location_name>San Francisco</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US06" confidence="0.888152003288269">California</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.888152003288269">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>37.7700004577637</latitude>
	    <longitude>-122.449996948242</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="unknown" class="Spot feature" mentions="1" confidence="0.606646001338959">
	    <location_name>Imperial Palace</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US32" confidence="0.184884995222092">Nevada</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.184884995222092">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>36.1181983947754</latitude>
	    <longitude>-115.171997070312</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.782507002353668">
	    <location_name>San Jose</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="CS08" confidence="0.677519977092743">San Jos Province</province>
	    <country fips_code="CS" iso_code="CR" confidence="0.677519977092743">Costa Rica</country>
	    <subregion>Central America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>9.93332958221436</latitude>
	    <longitude>-84.0832977294922</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="building" class="Spot feature" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Center for the Performing Arts</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US39" confidence="0.460209012031555">Ohio</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.460209012031555">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>39.5051002502441</latitude>
	    <longitude>-84.7319030761719</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">pop and hip-hop artist</property>
                <property name="person">Mike Posner Mike Posner</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="company">AOL</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">ProvinceOrState</property>
                <property name="value">California</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.191</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Holiday</property>
                <property name="value">New Year's Day</property>
                <property name="instances">4</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.760</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">URL</property>
                <property name="value">http://moanynye-bencabanas.eventbrite.com</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.241</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">All New</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.334</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">EmailAddress</property>
                <property name="value">djbencabanas@hotmail.com</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.241</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">The Regency Ballroom</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.108</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Currency</property>
                <property name="value">USD</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.423</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Eve Event</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.334</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Holiday</property>
                <property name="value">new year's eve</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.108</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">San Jose Center</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.145</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Mike Posner Mike Posner</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.241</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">Imperial Palace</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.145</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">pop and hip-hop artist</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.241</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">San Jose Center for the Performing Arts</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.145</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">Regency Ballroom</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.334</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Company</property>
                <property name="value">AOL</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.321</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761962">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Regarding Autumn 2010 Versions of the Petzl NOMIC and ERGO Ice Climbing Tools]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Normal GRIPREST adjustment system 

Normal GRIPREST adjustment system 

12/21/10 - It has come to our attention that the adjustment system of the GRIPREST (the lower hand rest at the bottom of the handle) on the 2010 NOMIC (U21 2) and ERGO (U22) in some cases may not stay fixed in the desired size position. 

This issue concerns NOMIC and ERGO ice tools with serial numbers between 10208 and 10329 and all GRIPREST (U21 GR2) accessory parts. It does not concern the new QUARKs or the older versions of the NOMICs, QUARKs and QUARK ERGOs. 

Following conversations with end users and extensive lab testing, we have determined that this problem can occur when an inward force is applied to the GRIPREST, damaging the adjustment teeth at the base of the tool’s handle that mesh with the GRIPREST (see photo). Once this damage occurs, users may lose the ability to fix the GRIPREST in the desired size position.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761962&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.climbing.com/news/press/regarding_autumn_2010_versions_of_the_petzl_nomic_and_ergo_ice_climbing_tools</original_link>
	<source>Climbing Magazine</source>
	<source_category>Consumer</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.climbing.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  4:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860084758</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Recreation</keyword>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">IndustryTerm</property>
                <property name="value">ice tools</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.857</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761963">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Turkish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[10:23 CHP'de üye olmayıp PM'ye seçilen kişilere yapılan itiraz da reddedildi]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[BazÄ± partililer, Ã‡ankaya â€™na bu iki iddiayla ilgili iki itirazda daha bulunmuÅŸtu. Ä°tirazlarÄ± gÃ¶rÃ¼ÅŸen Ã‡ankaya , itirazlarÄ± reddetti. daha Ã¶nce partinin 15. OlaÄŸanÃ¼stÃ¼ KurultayÄ±nda Parti Meclisiâ€™nin (PM) kadÄ±n kotasÄ±nÄ±n hesaplanma yÃ¶ntemine iliÅŸkin yapÄ±lan itirazÄ± da reddetmiÅŸti. da aynÄ± gerekÃ§eyle yapÄ±lan itirazÄ± reddetmiÅŸ ve Ã‡ankaya â€™nun kararÄ±nÄ±n mevzuata uygun gÃ¶rÃ¼ldÃ¼ÄŸÃ¼nÃ¼ bildirmiÅŸti.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761963&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.feedsportal.com/c/32727/f/510259/s/10d62120/l/0L0Smilliyet0N0Btr0Cchp0Ede0Euye0Eolmayip0Epm0Eye0Esecilen0Ekisilere0Eyapilan0Eitiraz0Eda0Ereddedildi0Csiyaset0Csondakika0C220B120B20A10A0C13294820Cdefault0Bhtm/story01.htm</original_link>
	<source>Milliyet</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.feedsportal.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>8</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>TURKEY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761964">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Naidu's fast enters sixth day, condition worsens]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[HYDERABAD: The condition of Telegu Desam Party President N Chandrababu Naidu worsened further today as he refused to consume even any liquid, on the sixth day of his indefinite hunger strike seeking justice for farmers. 

At one point Chandrababu, closed his room door from inside and did not let anyone venture inside. His wife Bhuvaneswari, family members and senior leaders of TDP tried to persuade Chandrababu to take some fluids but to no avail. 

A six-member team of expert doctors from NIMS is constantly monitoring the leader of the opposition. 

Doctors then wanted to shift the Leader of Opposition to the Intensive Care Unit, but he resisted that attempt as well. 

"We are now trying to convert the same room into an ICU," doctors at Nizam's Institute of Medical Sciences said. 

Chandrababu's nephews and film stars NTR (Junior) and Kalyan Ram visited him in the hospital today and pleaded with him to give up the fast in view of his health condition. 

"But he refused to heed. He looked very weak," they said. They strongly denounced the Congress government's indifferent attitude and said it should immediately take steps to resolve the issue. 

Meanwhile, TDP and Left parties gathered around the district Collectorates in the state demanding that the government concede the demands raised by Chandrababu and rescue the distressed farmers. 

Former Home Minister T Devender Goud and CPI state Secretary K Narayana led the siege at the Ranga Reddy district Collector's office here. They were taken into preventive custody along with scores of party workers. 

Information Technology professionals took out a march from KBR Park to NIMS in solidarity with Chandrababu Naidu. Thousands of farmers, people and TDP workers came to NIMS from different districts to see Chandrababu but were prevented from going inside the hospital block. 

Naidu is on an indefinite hunger strike in protest against the "inadequate" relief package announced by the state government for farmers who lost their crop in the recent rains.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761964&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/Naidus-fast-enters-sixth-day-condition-worsens/articleshow/7144261.cms</original_link>
	<source>Times of India</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>The Times Group</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860661568</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank type="front">28</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>INDIA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.982082009315491">
	    <location_name>HYDERABAD</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="IN02" confidence="0.967279970645905">Andhra Pradesh</province>
	    <country fips_code="IN" iso_code="IN" confidence="0.967279970645905">India</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>17.3752994537354</latitude>
	    <longitude>78.4744033813477</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="college" class="Spot feature" mentions="1" confidence="0.443260014057159">
	    <location_name>NIMS</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="IN09" confidence="0.219889998435974">Gujarat</province>
	    <country fips_code="IN" iso_code="IN" confidence="0.219889998435974">India</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>23.0394992828369</latitude>
	    <longitude>72.5662994384766</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="county" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>Ranga Reddy</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="IN02" confidence="0.992680013179779">Andhra Pradesh</province>
	    <country fips_code="IN" iso_code="IN" confidence="0.992680013179779">India</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>17.3199005126953</latitude>
	    <longitude>77.9311981201172</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="0.589960992336273">
	    <location_name>NIMS</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US37" confidence="0.162392005324364">North Carolina</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.162392005324364">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>35.3096008300781</latitude>
	    <longitude>-81.030403137207</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Kalyan Ram</property>
                <property name="instances">5</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.446</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">President</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.322</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Nizam's Institute of Medical Sciences</property>
                <property name="instances">4</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.696</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">CPI state Secretary</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.106</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Congress</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.152</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Telegu Desam Party</property>
                <property name="instances">4</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.739</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Technology</property>
                <property name="value">Information Technology</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.088</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Ranga Reddy district Collector</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.106</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">state government</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.063</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Company</property>
                <property name="value">KBR</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.088</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">HYDERABAD</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.322</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">leader</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.328</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">Home Minister</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.106</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Intensive Care Unit</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.309</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">Nizam's Institute of Medical Sciences</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.264</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Bhuvaneswari</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.318</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761968">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Nitrogént szállító tartálykocsi karambolozott]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[hvg@hvg.hu]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Tartálykocsi és személyautó ütközött Andornaktálya határában - közölte a rendőrség és a katasztrófavédelem. Cseppfolyós nitrogént szállító tartálykocsi és személyautó ütközött szerda reggel Andornaktálya határában, a balesetben egy ember megsérült, a nehézjármű rakományát nem érte károsodás.� A két jármű a község határától alig száz méterre karambolozott; az Andornaktályáról Mezőkövesdre vezető úton félpályás lezárás mellett helyszínel a rendőrség.

A megyei katasztrófavédelmi igazgatóság tájékoztatása szerint a tartálykocsi rakományát az ütközés következtében nem érte károsodás. A műszaki mentést a helyszínelés után kezdik meg.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761968&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://hvg.hu/itthon/20101222_tartalykocsi_balesete#rss</original_link>
	<source>Hvg.hu</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://hvg.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>2</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761970">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Chinese">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[志高商城正式上线 设专销机区别传统销售渠道]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[www.qq.com]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[志高商城截图（腾讯家电配图）腾讯家电讯（乔红康）北京时间12月22日消息，腾讯家电从志高获悉，由志高空调自身创建的“志高商城”B2C空调网购平台已于今天上午10点正式上线。据志高空调公共关系部部长黄通华介绍，志高商城上线比原定计划时间略有推迟，主要是因为网上商城属于新生事物，需要一定时间的试运用。黄通华介绍]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761970&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://tech.qq.com/a/20101222/000454.htm</original_link>
	<source>QQ.com</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://tech.qq.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>CHINA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>InformationTechnology</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP45</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS51</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761977">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Spanish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Tarifas del taxi suben un 1,76%]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Foto: EP Suben los servicios diurnos y nocturnos, se clarifican los suplementos y las vacaciones, y se adelanta el horario festivo los sábados 

MADRID, 22 Dic. (EUROPA PRESS) - 

Las tarifas del taxi en Madrid para el año 2011 subirán a partir de esta medianoche un 1,76 por ciento de media, como consecuencia entre otras cosas del incremento del precio de la bajada de bandera entre semana y por la nueva tarifa por inicio de viaje en domingos y festivos.

Así, dada la actual situación de crisis económica, el acuerdo entre el Consistorio y el sector limita la subida tarifaria a varios ajustes técnicos que, de media, suponen una subida porcentual del 1,76 por ciento.

Los aspectos mas destacables de las nuevas tarifas del 2011 son, por una parte, el incremento de 5 céntimos en la bajada de bandera diurna de lunes a sábado de 6 a 21 horas, periodo en que se pasa de 2,05 a 2,10 euros.

Además, se crea una nueva bajada de bandera específica para los domingos y festivos que se sitúa en 2,20 euros, y el precio por kilómetro de la tarifa 1 se eleva 2 céntimos, pasando de 0,98 a 1 euro.

Asimismo, la hora de servicio diurna (de 6 a 21 horas) pasa de 18,10 a 18,50 y la nocturna (de 21 a 6 horas) sube de 18,35 a 20 euros. Por su parte, el periodo vacacional de agosto será del 1 al 14 para unas licencias y del 16 al 30 para el resto, aunque el día 15 de agosto podrán trabajar todos. 

También se congelan todos los suplementos, y se clarifican los supuestos en los que se pueden cobrar el suplemento del Aeropuerto de Barajas, que sólo lo será en los viajes con origen o destino a las terminales de pasajeros.

Por su parte, el suplemento de estaciones de autobuses y ferrocarril sólo se podrá cobrar en los viajes con origen en las mismas, suprimiéndose el mismo en los viajes con destino a aquéllas; y se elimina el suplemento especial de la noche de Reyes, manteniéndose únicamente el de Nochebuena y Nochevieja.

Por último, los sábados se considerarán festivos a efectos tarifarios a partir de las 15 horas, frente a la estipulación actual, que marca que el inicio de la tarifa festiva comienza a las 17 horas.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761977&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.europapress.es/madrid/noticia-tarifas-taxi-suben-176-incremento-bajada-bandera-diurna-nueva-tarifa-domingo-festivo-20101222053829.html</original_link>
	<source>Europa Press</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.europapress.es</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3856689438</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>7</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>SPAIN</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="MTAA">
	    <name>Dada</name>
	    <symbol>DA</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.994737982749939">
	    <location_name>MADRID</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.437626987695694">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.437626987695694">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4000015258789</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.68333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="national capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.994759976863861">
	    <location_name>Madrid</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="SP29" confidence="0.991484999656677">Madrid Autonomous Community</province>
	    <country fips_code="SP" iso_code="ES" confidence="0.991484999656677">Spain</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Europe</subregion>
	    <region>Europe</region>
	    <latitude>40.4000015258789</latitude>
	    <longitude>-3.68333005905151</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761983">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Orbán: a jegybank és a kormány szembenállása kárt okoz az országnak]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Független Hírügynökség]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[A miniszterelnök szerint "két különböző malomban őröl a kormány és a Nemzeti Bank" Orbán Viktor az MTV Az Este című műsorában egyebek között azt mondta: kárt okoz az országnak, hogy a jegybanknak egészen más az álláspontja a gazdaságpolitikáról. 

A miniszterelnök szerint "két különböző malomban őröl a kormány és a Nemzeti Bank" Orbán Viktor a Magyar Televízió Az Este című műsorában egyebek között azt mondta: kárt okoz az országnak, ha a jegybanknak egészen más az álláspontja a gazdaságpolitikáról, mint a kormánynak. Arra a kérdésre, hogy miért nem hajlandó találkozni és tárgyalni Simor András jegybank elnökkel, a kormányfő azt mondta: "miután a kívánatos gazdaságpolitika irányáról a jegybanknak más elgondolása van, mint a kabinetnek, éppen elég, ha a nemzetgazdasági miniszter beszél a nemzeti bank vezetőjével." Orbán Viktor az interjúban megerősítette: az évtized végénél előbb nem várható az euró magyarországi bevezetése.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761983&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221941</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>7</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XNYS">
	    <name>Viacom, Inc.</name>
	    <symbol>VIA</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761984">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="French">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[La Corée du Sud annonce des exercices militaires sans précédent]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Navire de la marine sud-coréenne en patrouille au large de l'île de Yeonpyeong, cible de tirs d'artillerie de la Corée du Nord ayant fait quatre morts en novembre. L'armée sud-coréenne annonce qu'elle procèdera à partir de jeudi à des vastes manoeuvres terrestres -en plus des manoeuvres navales déjà initiées en mer Jaune- dont les plus importants exercices à munitions réelles jamais effectués sur son territoire à proximité de la frontière avec la Corée du Nord. 

(c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2010]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761984&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.paris-normandie.fr/article/france-monde/la-coree-du-sud-annonce-des-exercices-militaires-sans-precedent</original_link>
	<source>Paris-Normandie</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.paris-normandie.fr</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860530776</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>2</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>FRANCE</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XTSE">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
            <company exchange="XNYS">
	    <name>Thomson Reuters Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>TRI</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761985">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Italian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Vende alcol ai ragazziniNei guai un barista di Como]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[COMO - Nel suo locale venivano vendute bevande alcoliche a ragazzini di età inferiore ai 16 anni e così il titolare di un bar di via Diaz è stato denunciato dalla polizia locale. Adesso rischia, oltre a un'ammenda molto pesante, la sospensione della licenza. 

Sul locale, ha fatto sapere il Comune, «sono in corso ulteriori accertamenti da parte degli inquirenti». Il nome del bar, per il momento, non è stato reso noto. «La polizia locale - aggiungono da Palazzo Cernezzi - ha effettuato diversi controlli contestando l'articolo 689 del codice penale al titolare del locale e a chi stava servendo al banco. Ora sarà il giudice a stabilire la fondatezza del reato contestato. La denuncia effettuata - specifica la nota - segue le verifiche promosse nei locali cittadini dall'amministrazione in collaborazione con la Procura, la polizia locale e il settore Attività produttive del Comune». 

Non si tratta del primo locale della città finito nel mirino per la vendita di alcolici a minori di 16 anni (la legge lo vieta). Alla fine di ottobre lo stesso abuso era stato contestato, infatti, al titolare del «Mangu» di via Milano 138. Tra le violazioni riscontrate c'era, in quel caso, la presenza nel locale di avventori under 16 con tasso alcolico pari a 0,42. 

Il già citato articolo 689 del codice penale dice che «l'esercente il quale somministra bevande alcooliche a un minore degli anni sedici, è punito con l'arresto fino a un anno». E prevede un aumento della pena «se dal fatto deriva l'ubriachezza». In ogni caso, «la condanna importa la sospensione dall'esercizio». Le stesse regole, peraltro, valgono non soltanto per gli avventori con meno di 16 anni, ma anche in caso di «persona che appaia affetta da malattia di mente, o che si trovi in manifeste condizioni di deficienza psichica a causa di un'altra infermità». 

«Nelle scorse settimane - sottolineano dal Comune - sono state riscontrate anche irregolarità in una discoteca. In questo caso l'attività, dopo una sospensione di alcuni giorni, è già ripresa (le contestazioni riguardavano la sicurezza degli avventori e il disturbo della quiete pubblica)». 

Il Tar ha invece accolto - è notizia di ieri - la richiesta di sospensiva presentata dai legali del bar «Est est est» di via Tommaso Grossi, dando torto al Comune che aveva contestato il volume troppo alto della musica. La campagna di controlli a tappeto voluta da Palazzo Cernezzi, comunque, prosegue.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761985&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it/stories/Cronaca/175538_vende_alcol_ai_ragazzini_nei_guai_un_barista_di_como/</original_link>
	<source>La Provincia di Como</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>4</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>ITALY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860761998">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Interaction of anger with anxiety and responses to emotional facial expressions]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[My Library Conferences Resources Jobs MDLinx Blog CME Articles Full Text Articles Evidence Based Medicine Articles Clinical Articles]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860761998&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.mdlinx.com/PsychLinx/xml-article.cfm/3405812</original_link>
	<source>MDLinx</source>
	<source_category>Trade</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.mdlinx.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:02AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>18</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>AMERICAS</region>
	  <subregion>NORTHERN AMERICA</subregion>
	  <country>UNITED STATES</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>HealthCare</keyword>
	  <keyword>Professional</keyword>
	  <keyword>Medical</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code>
	  <keyword_code>SP35</keyword_code>
	  <keyword_code>NAICS62</keyword_code>
          </keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762003">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Kamionstop lesz az ünnepek alatt]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[hvg@hvg.hu]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Korlátozzák a nehéz tehergépjárművek forgalmát a karácsony és szilveszter környéki munkaszüneti napokon és hétvégéken - közölte a Nemzeti Fejlesztési Minisztérium szerdán. A közlemény szerint a jogszabály hatálya alá tartozó járművek Magyarország közútjain december 24-én, pénteken 22 órától 24 óráig, december 25-én, szombaton 8 órától, december 26-án, vasárnap 22 óráig, illetve 2011. január 1-én, szombaton 8 órától, január 2-án,� vasárnap 22 óráig nem közlekedhetnek.� A kormány novemberben döntött a kamionstop előírásainak módosításáról, a felmentési szabályok pontosításáról. A korlátozás alól felmentést kapnak a gyógyászati célú gázok szállítását végző, valamint a közüzemi és közérdekű beruházásokhoz használt tehergépkocsik.� A közlemény szerint az éves felmentés - kérelem esetén - a következő év január 31-ig tartó hatállyal is kiadható. A kérelmet nemcsak a jármű üzemben tartója, hanem a megrendelő is előterjesztheti.� A változások 2011. január elsején lépnek hatályba.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762003&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://hvg.hu/itthon/20101222_kamionstop_karacsony#rss</original_link>
	<source>Hvg.hu</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://hvg.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>3</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Society</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762016">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[No. 89: UConn tops UCLA, beats Florida St 93-62]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[HARTFORD, Conn. – Men's teams. Women's teams. No. 89 belongs to UConn. It beats them all.

The No. 1-ranked Huskies women's basketball team topped the 88-game winning streak set by John Wooden's UCLA men's team from 1971-74, beating No. 22 Florida State 93-62 on Tuesday night. Playing with the relentlessness that has become its trademark — and would have made Wooden proud — Connecticut blew past the Seminoles as it has so many other teams in the last 2 1/2 years.

"I don't want my team to compare themselves to anyone," UConn coach Geno Auriemma said afterward. "I'm not John Wooden and this isn't UCLA. This is Connecticut and that's good enough."

Maya Moore had a career-high 41 points and 10 rebounds and freshman Bria Hartley added 21 points for the Huskies, who have not lost since April 6, 2008, in the NCAA tournament semifinals. Only twice during the record run has a team come within single digits of UConn — Stanford in the NCAA championship game last season and Baylor in early November.

When the final buzzer sounded, UConn players sprinted across the floor to shake hands with the student section as fans held up "89" signs and "89" balloons bobbed in the stands behind center court. Two other fans raised a banner that read "The Sorcerer of Storrs" — a play on Wooden's nickname, "The Wizard of Westwood."

After a brief huddle in front of their bench, UConn players re-emerged wearing "89 and Counting" T-shirts. As fans roared, the players bounced around the court before posing for photos.

It's one more chapter of history for UConn, and perhaps the grandest.

"It's pretty amazing. It really is," said Auriemma, at a rare loss for words.

Asked what he would recall from the incredible run, he mentioned a pair of experienced stars on this team: "I'll probably remember Maya Moore and Tiffany Hayes. And how incredibly difficult it is to play that many games in a row and win 'em all."

Connecticut long ago established itself as the marquee program in the women's game, the benchmark by which all others are measured. The Huskies already own seven national titles and four perfect seasons under Auriemma, and they've produced a galaxy of stars that includes Rebecca Lobo, Diana Taurasi, Jennifer Rizzotti, Sue Bird and Tina Charles.

The streak, though, takes it to another level, certainly raising the profile of women's basketball and maybe all of women's athletics.

Two days after beating No. 11 Ohio State to tie UCLA, UConn toppled the mark in front of a sellout crowd of 16,294 at the XL Center that included Wooden's grandson, Greg, attending his first women's game.

"My grandfather would have been thrilled. He would have been absolutely thrilled to see his streak broken by a women's basketball team," the 47-year-old Wooden said. "He thought, especially in the last 10 years, that the best basketball was played at the collegiate level — and it wasn't by the men."

John Wooden was 99 when he died last June 4.

There was a festive atmosphere throughout the city, where building lights gleamed blue and white, and it was as electric as any Final Four inside the arena. Charles and UConn men's star Kemba Walker sat behind the Huskies' bench, and football coach Randy Edsall was there, too. Former NFL star Warrick Dunn, meanwhile, was cheering for his alma mater, Florida State.

With the game tied at 6, Moore and UConn (11-0) took command. The senior All-American had seven points during a 15-2 run to give Connecticut its first double-digit lead, and Moore's fadeaway jumper from the baseline extended the advantage to 34-15. Florida State (9-3) made a quick run to cut the lead to 11, but the Huskies weren't about to let anyone spoil this night.

UConn ripped off the next 16 points, capped by consecutive 3-pointers from Hartley and a pull-up by Moore. Auriemma gave Hartley a kiss at the next timeout, and the tough-to-please coach was still grinning at halftime.

"She doesn't feel any of this," Auriemma said as he left the court. "She's kind of immune to all of this as a freshman. I love kids like that." 

With a minute left to play and victory assured, Moore stood up and whirled a towel around her head. The All-American tossed it in the air briefly before sitting down for the final seconds, beaming as she and her teammates on the bench yelled encouragement at the players on the floor. 

"All you guys from Florida State, it wasn't easy to be part of all of this," Auriemma said. "I hope you don't feel disrespected by all this. You played a heck of a game." 

UConn's rise to prominence began in 1995, when Lobo led the Huskies to their first national championship and unbeaten season. Since then, the best players in the country have made their way to the rural campus in Storrs, 30 miles outside of Hartford. 

The excellence and confidence that defines great teams defines this one because Auriemma won't have it any other way. Perfection is expected, not simply a goal, and Auriemma goes to extraordinary lengths to get it. 

He goads his players with criticisms of their games — sarcastic remarks that may strike outsiders as harsh but somehow trigger just the right response with gusto. He makes them play games of seven-on-five in practice. He rounds up bigger, stronger male students around campus to serve as practice players. He runs endless drills to hone skills the players thought they had mastered in junior high. 

It hardly seems to matter who is on the floor because UConn players don't wear names on the back of their uniforms. The only one that counts is the one on the front. 

When UConn — led by Taurasi — won 70 straight games from 2001-03, a record in the women's game, it seemed unfathomable that it would be toppled, like UCLA's 88. But what fans have learned over the years is that nothing this team does should be surprising. The Huskies have beaten 16 top-10 teams during the latest streak — four more than UCLA did during its run — and five of those wins came against the No. 2 team. It's been more than 17 years since UConn lost consecutive games. 

"We never talked about the streak," said Charles, last season's national player of the year. "We were playing for each other, what we did at practice, all the hard work we did, and just trying to do it on the court. There wasn't anything about the streak." 

The Huskies have won by any average of more than 33 points during the streak and rarely found themselves in trouble. They have trailed for 134 minutes, including only 13 in the second half. They've won back-to-back national championships, and are now one short of Tennessee's record for overall titles by a women's team. 

Even before UConn tied UCLA's record, the two programs were linked. 

Auriemma acknowledges that his team runs the same offense that Wooden perfected 37 years earlier. But it's not just the Xs and Os. The top block of Wooden's pyramid of success reads: "Competitive Greatness: Perform at your best when your best is required. Your best is required every day." 

That's been Auriemma's mantra. 

Greg Wooden, who lives in California, said he came East because, "I kind of thought that somebody should come here from the family and show support." 

He also was aware that "certain players have said they're not really supportive of the streak." 

But he came knowing "my grandfather would have loved to have been here to see this." 

The day Notre Dame broke UCLA's streak, John Wooden was asked how long it would be before somebody surpassed it. 

"I have no idea how long it will be before somebody else wins that many. I know it takes at least three years," he replied. 

Try 36 years, 11 months, and 2 days.

(Agencies)]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762016&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://english.sina.com/sports/p/2010/1221/353011.html</original_link>
	<source>SINA</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>SINA Corporation</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://english.sina.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3859849539</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>7</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>CHINA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Sports'>
	    <category>Sports: latest</category>
	    <category>Sports: latest scores</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Consumer</keyword>
	  <keyword>Sports</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker>
            <company exchange="XOTC">
	    <name>First National Corporation</name>
	    <symbol>FXNC</symbol>
            </company>
          </stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="province" class="Administrative region" mentions="5" confidence="0.92824399471283">
	    <location_name>Florida</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US12" confidence="0.78983598947525">Florida</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.78983598947525">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>28.7504997253418</latitude>
	    <longitude>-82.5000991821289</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="1">
	    <location_name>HARTFORD, Conn.</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US09" confidence="0.881790995597839">Connecticut</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.881790995597839">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>41.7636985778809</latitude>
	    <longitude>-72.6850967407227</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="college" class="Spot feature" mentions="1" confidence="0.959921002388">
	    <location_name>UConn</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US09" confidence="0.264820992946625">Connecticut</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.264820992946625">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>41.8092994689941</latitude>
	    <longitude>-72.2537002563477</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="province" class="Administrative region" mentions="4" confidence="0.999961972236633">
	    <location_name>Connecticut</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US09" confidence="0.918416976928711">Connecticut</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.918416976928711">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>41.6669998168945</latitude>
	    <longitude>-72.6664962768555</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="2" confidence="0.99848198890686">
	    <location_name>Storrs</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US09" confidence="0.372426003217697">Connecticut</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.372426003217697">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>41.8083992004395</latitude>
	    <longitude>-72.2494964599609</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="city" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.484182000160217">
	    <location_name>Westwood</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US34" confidence="0.395588010549545">New Jersey</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.395588010549545">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>40.9911994934082</latitude>
	    <longitude>-74.032600402832</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.975439012050629">
	    <location_name>Hartford</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US09" confidence="0.971759021282196">Connecticut</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.971759021282196">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>41.7636985778809</latitude>
	    <longitude>-72.6850967407227</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="province" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999863982200623">
	    <location_name>Tennessee</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US47" confidence="0.859763979911804">Tennessee</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.859763979911804">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>35.750301361084</latitude>
	    <longitude>-86.2502975463867</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="province" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.997461020946503">
	    <location_name>California</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="US06" confidence="0.987694025039673">California</province>
	    <country fips_code="US" iso_code="US" confidence="0.987694025039673">United States</country>
	    <subregion>Northern America</subregion>
	    <region>Americas</region>
	    <latitude>37.2501983642578</latitude>
	    <longitude>-119.750999450684</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">he came East because, "I kind of thought that somebody should come here from the family and show support.</property>
                <property name="person">Greg Wooden</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">UConn coach</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="organization">UCLA</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">FamilyRelation</property>
                <property name="person_relative">Greg Wooden</property>
                <property name="person">John Wooden</property>
                <property name="familyrelationtype">grandson</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">We never talked about the streak; We were playing for each other, what we did at practice, all the hard work we did, and just trying to do it on the court. There wasn't anything about the streak.</property>
                <property name="persondescription">national player</property>
                <property name="person">Tina Charles</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonAttributes</property>
                <property name="gender">M</property>
                <property name="age">47</property>
                <property name="person">John Wooden</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">his team runs the same offense that Wooden perfected 37 years earlier.</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">a pair of experienced stars on thisteam: "I'll probably remember Maya Moore and Tiffany Hayes</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">All you guys from Florida State, it wasn't easy to be part of all of this; I hope you don't feel disrespected by all this. You played a heck of a game.</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">I don't want my team to compare themselves to anyone; I'm not John Wooden and this isn't UCLA. This is Connecticut and that's good enough.</property>
                <property name="persondescription">UConn coach</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">It's pretty amazing.; It really is</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">football coach</property>
                <property name="person">Randy Edsall</property>
                <property name="organization">UCLA</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">current</property>
                <property name="position">national player</property>
                <property name="person">Tina Charles</property>
                <property name="careertype">professional</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">I have no idea how long it will be before somebody else wins that many.; I know it takes at least three years</property>
                <property name="person">John Wooden</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">Quotation</property>
                <property name="quote">She doesn't feel any of this; She's kind of immune to all of this as a freshman. I love kids like that.</property>
                <property name="person">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">UCLA</property>
                <property name="instances">8</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.676</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Diana Taurasi</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.389</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">ProvinceOrState</property>
                <property name="value">Tennessee</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.074</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Sue Bird</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.263</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">John Wooden</property>
                <property name="instances">13</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.698</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsGame</property>
                <property name="value">basketball</property>
                <property name="instances">4</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.484</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Greg Wooden</property>
                <property name="instances">8</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.484</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Tina Charles</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.488</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsGame</property>
                <property name="value">football</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.220</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Maya Moore</property>
                <property name="instances">11</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.557</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">national player</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.081</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">City</property>
                <property name="value">HARTFORD</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.481</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Tiffany Hayes</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.275</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">football coach</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.220</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Geno Auriemma</property>
                <property name="instances">19</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.730</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Randy Edsall</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.220</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Kemba Walker</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.220</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Warrick Dunn</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.215</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">coach</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.181</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Jennifer Rizzotti</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.263</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Bria Hartley</property>
                <property name="instances">3</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.453</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsGame</property>
                <property name="value">athletics</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.256</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsLeague</property>
                <property name="value">NFL</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.212</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Rebecca Lobo</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.333</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">UConn coach</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.306</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">ProvinceOrState</property>
                <property name="value">California</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.055</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">ProvinceOrState</property>
                <property name="value">Connecticut</property>
                <property name="instances">5</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.549</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">SportsLeague</property>
                <property name="value">NCAA</property>
                <property name="instances">2</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.303</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">National Football League</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.212</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Organization</property>
                <property name="value">Stanford</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.294</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Facility</property>
                <property name="value">XL Center</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.249</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762018">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="English">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Upside inflation risk remains: RBI]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[, a poll shows. Full Article A vendor arranges packets of pulses at a wholesale market in Chandigarh December 11, 2009. 

Credit: Reuters/Ajay Verma/Files The RBI left interest rates on hold last Thursday at its mid-quarter review but warned inflation was still well above its comfort level and unveiled steps to address persistently tight liquidity, adding to the possibility that it will resume monetary tightening in January. 

India's headline inflation eased in line with expectations to 7.48 percent in November, its lowest level in a year. Kaushik Basu, the chief economic adviser to the finance ministry said on Tuesday the headline inflation in January is expected to be lower than the November level. 

(Reporting by Suvashree Dey Choudhury; editing by Malini Menon)]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762018&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://in.reuters.com/article/idINIndia-53723820101222</original_link>
	<source>Reuters India</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher>Thomson Reuters</publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://in.reuters.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>1</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank type="front">42</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>INDIA</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster>
            <channel name = 'Regional'>
	    <category>India news</category>
            </channel>
          </cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Global</keyword>
	  <keyword>Geographic</keyword>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
            <location type="provincial capital" class="Populated place" mentions="1" confidence="0.865505993366241">
	    <location_name>Chandigarh</location_name>
	    <province fips_code="IN05" confidence="0.861840009689331">Chandigarh</province>
	    <country fips_code="IN" iso_code="IN" confidence="0.861840009689331">India</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>30.7343006134033</latitude>
	    <longitude>76.7932968139648</longitude>
            </location>
            <location type="country" class="Administrative region" mentions="1" confidence="0.999997973442078">
	    <location_name>India</location_name>
	    <province></province>
	    <country fips_code="IN" iso_code="IN" confidence="0.963003993034363">India</country>
	    <subregion>Southern Asia</subregion>
	    <region>Asiapac</region>
	    <latitude>20</latitude>
	    <longitude>77</longitude>
            </location>
          </metacarta>
          <open_calais_data>
            <events_and_facts>
              <event_or_fact>
                <property name="type">PersonCareer</property>
                <property name="status">past</property>
                <property name="position">chief economic adviser</property>
                <property name="person">Kaushik Basu</property>
                <property name="careertype">political</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
              </event_or_fact>
            </events_and_facts>
            <entities>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Ajay Verma</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.417</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">IndustryTerm</property>
                <property name="value">finance ministry</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.214</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">chief economic adviser to the finance</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.214</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Country</property>
                <property name="value">India</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.341</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Person</property>
                <property name="value">Kaushik Basu</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.214</property>
              </entity>
              <entity>
                <property name="type">Position</property>
                <property name="value">chief economic adviser</property>
                <property name="instances">1</property>
                <property name="relevance">0.214</property>
              </entity>
            </entities>
          </open_calais_data>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762019">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Turkish">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[10:22 Leylekler hala göç etmedi]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Baharın müjdecisi olarak bilinen leylekler, bu yıl Iğdır’dan göç etmedi. 

Doğu Anadolu Bölgesi’ndeki illerin çoğunda soğuk hava etkili olurken Iğdır’da yazdan kalma günler yaşanıyor. Sıcak havanın da etkisiyle, kentteki yaklaşık 100 leylek, bu yıl başka ülkelere gitmedi. 

Çevre ve Orman İl Müdürü Taner Tazegün, "İlk defa bu kadar leylek sıcak ülkelere göç etmedi. Önceki yıllarda sadece yaşlı ve göç edemeyecek durumda olan birkaç leylek kalıyordu. Bu yıl 100’e yakın leylek hala kentimizde" dedi. 

Tazegün, "Hava sıcaklığı bu yıl mevsim normallerinin üzerinde seyrediyor. Leylekler, kışın da ılık geçeceğini düşündükleri için gitmedi. Kentte fare sayısında bir artış oldu. Leyleklerin gitmemesini bir neden olarak da buna bağlayabiliriz. Bu saatten sonra da leyleklerin göç etmeleri biraz zor olabilir. Çünkü göç edecekleri güzergahlarda soğuk hava etkili oluyor. Sadece Nahçivan üzerinden göç edebilirler" diye konuştu.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762019&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://rss.feedsportal.com/c/32727/f/510259/s/10d62121/l/0L0Smilliyet0N0Btr0Cleylekler0Ehala0Egoc0Eetmedi0Cturkiye0Csondakika0C220B120B20A10A0C13294810Cdefault0Bhtm/story01.htm</original_link>
	<source>Milliyet</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://rss.feedsportal.com</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>9</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>ASIAPAC</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN ASIA</subregion>
	  <country>TURKEY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>Miscellaneous</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762027">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Hungarian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Fegyveres az egyik kaliforniai tévében]]></hltext_display>
		<author><![CDATA[Független Hírügynökség]]></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Rövid rábeszélés után megadta magát a rohamrendőröknek egy nő, a kaliforniai Charlotte egyik kábeltelevíziójának székházában, ahol fegyverrel a kezében jelent meg a kedd esti hírműsor idején. 

Rövid rábeszélés után megadta magát a rohamrendőröknek egy nő, a kaliforniai Charlotte egyik kábeltelevíziójának székházában, ahol fegyverrel a kezében jelent meg a kedd esti hírműsor idején. A rendőrség közlése szerint azonnal leállították az adást, amikor a nő elővette a fegyvert, amit a saját fejéhez nyomott a WSOC-TV épületének előcsarnokában. 

A rendőrség azt közölte, hogy az incidensben senki nem sérült meg. A rendőrök kiürítették az épületet, és a tévé munkatársait a parkoló hátsó, védett részébe vitték minden eshetőségre felkészülve. 

"Nincs adás, egy zavarodott nő van az előcsarnokban, a rendőrök körülvették az épületet, a személyzetet kimenekítették"- ezt írta az incidens idején a Twitteren Blair Miller műsorvezető. A rendőrség először azt közölte, hogy eldördült egy lövés, Rodney Monroe rendőrfőnök azonban később azt mondta, hogy nem volt lövés, mivel a nő fegyvere nem volt töltve. 

A bejelentés szerint a nő a tévé portását fenyegette meg először, majd a saját fejéhez emelte a fegyvert. A csatorna szerint a nő neve Wendy Naidas. Egyelőre nem tudni, mit akart. A WSOC-TV egy órával a nő őrizetbe vétele után újraindította adását.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762027&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.webradio.hu/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=221947</original_link>
	<source>Webradio</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.webradio.hu</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>8</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>EASTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>HUNGARY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762030">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="German">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Debatte um FDP-Chef Westerwelle dauert an]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[Bild vergrößern Nach dem neuerlichen Umfrage-Absturz der FDP versuchen führende Liberale, die Debatte über Parteichef Guido Westerwelle zu beruhigen. Entwicklungsminister Dirk Niebel mahnte, die FDP könne nur bestehen, wenn sie zusammenhalte. Gisela Piltz, stellvertretende Parteivorsitzende in Nordrhein-Westfalen, betonte, öffentliche Personaldebatten lösten keine Probleme. Der Vorsitzende der Jungen Liberalen, Lasse Becker, forderte Westerwelle aber auch zur Selbstkritik auf. Becker appellierte an den Parteichef, beim Dreikönigstreffen in Stuttgart «selbstkritisch den einen oder anderen Fehler zu benennen». Zudem solle Westerwelle «die Menschen emotionaler als in der Vergangenheit ansprechen», sagte der FDP-Nachwuchspolitiker den «Stuttgarter Nachrichten» (Mittwoch). Von den Wahlergebnissen im Frühjahr 2011 hänge viel ab. «Und beim Bundesparteitag wird analysiert: Wer hat welchen Fehler gemacht, und wie baue ich ein zukunftsfähiges Team.» Becker forderte zugleich eine inhaltliche Neuausrichtung der FDP: «Jedenfalls wird man nicht dadurch glaubwürdig, dass man zum 200. Mal eine Steuersenkung ankündigt. Wir brauchen einen Schwerpunkt beim Thema Haushaltskonsolidierung.» Die FDP müsse zudem klare Positionen bei der Ablehnung der Vorratsdatenspeicherung und dem Umbau der Sozialsysteme beziehen. «Und wir müssen uns beim Thema nachhaltige, ökologische Marktwirtschaft ein neues Feld erschließen.» Niebel machte deutlich, dass er jüngeren FDP-Politikern den Parteivorsitz noch nicht zutraut. Die FDP habe zwar eine hervorragende Führungsreserve, sagte er dem «Hamburger Abendblatt» (Mittwoch). «Ich denke allerdings, dass wir denen noch etwas Zeit geben sollten, um ihre Fähigkeiten zu veredeln.» Vom Dreikönigstreffen erwarte er «ein Aufbruchsignal, das weit über Stuttgart hinaus in der Republik sichtbar sein wird», so Niebel. «Ich bin felsenfest davon überzeugt, dass Guido Westerwelle eine mitreißende Rede halten wird.» Auch Piltz forderte ein Ende der Personaldebatte. Die Geschichte der FDP zeige eindrucksvoll, dass Personaldebatten in kritischen Situationen noch nie geholfen hätten, sagte die nordrhein- westfälische Partei-Vize «Handelsblatt Online». «Die FDP hat im Team gewonnen, und die FDP muss auch im Team Krisen meistern.» In der jüngsten Forsa-Umfrage ist die FDP auf drei Prozent abgesackt. (Quelle: Berlin (dpa/lby))]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762030&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.antenne.de/nachrichten/politik/artikel/303061/Debatte-um-FDP-Chef-Westerwelle-dauert-an.html</original_link>
	<source>Antenne</source>
	<source_category>National</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.antenne.de</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group>3860578077</duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>1</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>WESTERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>GERMANY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
	  <keyword>National</keyword>
	  <keyword>Geographic</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
        <article id="_3860762041">
           <description charset="UTF-8" language="Italian">
		<hltext_display><![CDATA[Cantù, gli auguri del Comuneora arrivano solo via mail]]></hltext_display>
		<author></author>
		<content><![CDATA[ora arrivano solo via mail 

CANTU' - Niente biglietti d'auguri (Foto by Archive) 

CANTU' - Niente biglietti, niente buste, niente francobolli. Leggi risparmiare la vita a qualche albero e soprattutto far risparmiare un non disprezzabile gruzzoletto alle casse comunali. Tanto più oggi che fondi proprio non ce ne sono. E allora anche il Comune di Cantù, come una bella fetta dei privati cittadini, ha sostituito il cartoncino natalizio adornato d'agrifoglio e renne in corsa con una e mail. Costo zero, e a dirla tutta s'azzera anche il rischio che gli auguri arrivino in tempo per primavera, con le rondini. Tutt'altro che remoto. 

L'idea, dice l'assessore all'innovazione tecnologica Marco Gallo, è partita dal sindaco Tiziana Sala, che ha rimarcato la necessità di tagliare costi e carta in viaggio. E gli uffici si sono adeguati. Tanto più che sprone identico è arrivato dal ministro per la Pubblica amministrazione Renato Brunetta, che ha invitato tutte le amministrazioni pubbliche a utilizzare la posta elettronica per lo scambio degli auguri in occasione delle festività natalizie, ispirato, si legge sul sito del dicastero, da un telegramma di buon onomastico ricevuto da un prefetto. Risultato, le scrivanie degli uffici comunali si sono fatte parecchio più sgombre. Altro che i tempi in cui a quest'ora s'erano già riempite scatole di biglietti. A venire inviato ad amministrazioni e autorità, un messaggio virtuale, corredato da un'immagine della ex chiesa di Sant'Ambrogio. Qualche Comune del Canturino, in verità, non ha fatto altrettanto. C'è da dire che i bigliettini scelti, di solito, hanno finalità benefica. Ma meglio non dirlo comunque a Brunetta.]]></content>
		</description>
	<url>http://c.moreover.com/click/here.pl?z3860762041&amp;z=1250248772</url>
	<original_link>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it/stories/Cronaca/175501_cant_gli_auguri_del_comune_ora_arrivano_solo_via_mail/</original_link>
	<source>La Provincia di Como</source>
	<source_category>Local</source_category>
	<genre>General</genre>
	<publisher></publisher>
	<media_type>text</media_type>
	<docurl>http://www.laprovinciadicomo.it</docurl>
	<harvest_time>Dec 22 2010  9:03AM</harvest_time>
	<valid_time>Jan 31 2011  9:03AM</valid_time>
	<access_registration></access_registration>
	<access_status></access_status>
	<duplicate_group></duplicate_group>
          <rank>
	  <source_rank>3</source_rank>
	  <web_rank>0</web_rank>
	  <order_rank>3</order_rank>
          </rank>
          <location>
	  <region>EUROPE</region>
	  <subregion>SOUTHERN EUROPE</subregion>
	  <country>ITALY</country>
	  <state></state>
	  <zip_area></zip_area>
	  <zip_code></zip_code>
          </location>
          <cluster></cluster>
          <keywords_public>
	  <keyword>News</keyword>
	  <keyword>Standard</keyword>
          </keywords_public>
          <keywords_code></keywords_code>
          <stock_ticker></stock_ticker>
          <metacarta>
          </metacarta>
	</article>
    </moreovercontentdump>